<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>SitCEN news</title>
	<link>https://github.com/Lensver65/Yanac/blob/main/SitCEN_News.xml</link>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025</lastBuildDate>
	<description>Latest news for SitCEN</description>
	<skipDays>
		<day>Saturday</day>
		<day>Sunday</day>
	</skipDays>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Chinese "Salt Typhoon" Hackers Exploit Exchange Vulnerabilities to Target Organizations</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Chinese APT group Salt Typhoon has been targeting critical sectors worldwide. They are known for their sophisticated cyberespionage capabilities and use multiple backdoors and hacking tools to maintain persistent access while minimizing detection. The group exploits vulnerabilities like Microsoft Exchange's ProxyLogon, PowerShell downgrade attacks, and public cloud services. AttackIQ developed an assessment template that emulates Salt Typhoon’s tactics to evaluate security controls against these threats. Continuous validation of detection and prevention pipelines is essential for mitigating the risks posed by Salt Typhoon's espionage operations.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://gbhackers.com/chinese-salt-typhoon-hackers-exploit-exchange-vulnerabilities/">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://gbhackers.com/chinese-salt-typhoon-hackers-exploit-exchange-vulnerabilities/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Red Canary Report Surfaces Sharp Increase in Cyberattacks Involving Identity</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Red Canary's analysis of 93,000 threats published this week found that cyberattacks seeking to compromise an identity increased by a factor of four in 2024. The most common result was the installation of info-stealer software used for exfiltration. Cybercriminals are shifting tactics and techniques to gain access to centralized systems through which they can steal data or distribute malware, making it clear that cybercriminals are becoming more sophisticated. The report also noted that 95% of those incidents occurred prior to Apple remediating a Gatekeeper bypass technique last September, compared to only 5% that occurred throughout the rest of the year.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://securityboulevard.com/2025/03/red-canary-report-surfaces-sharp-increase-in-cyberattacks-involving-identity/">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securityboulevard.com/2025/03/red-canary-report-surfaces-sharp-increase-in-cyberattacks-involving-identity/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Signal Messenger Misused for Targeted Attacks on Defense Industry Employees</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has identified a surge in targeted cyberattacks targeting employees and members of the Defense Forces. These attacks involve the use of Signal messenger apps for malware distribution, specifically the DarkCrystal RAT, which is a remote access trojan capable of executing arbitrary commands, stealing sensitive data, and establishing persistent control over infected systems. §Attackers are using compromised Signal accounts to send phishing messages that appear as meeting reports. The campaign has been active since at least the summer of 2024, with recent lures focusing on unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs), electronic warfare systems, and other military technologies. The use of popular messengers like Signal significantly expands the attack surface by creating uncontrolled channels for information exchange. This makes it challenging to detect threats using standard cyber protection tools. CERT-UA emphasizes the importance of vigilance and encourages users to report suspicious messages immediately. The agency also highlights the need for enhanced security measures to counter such sophisticated attacks. Recommendations for Enhanced Security include turning off automatic downloads of attachments, regularly checking linked devices, keeping software up-to-date, and enabling two-factor authentication.
		<p><a href="https://cyberpress.org/signal-messenger-misused-for-targeted-attacks/">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cyberpress.org/signal-messenger-misused-for-targeted-attacks/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>WhatsApp fixed zero-day flaw used to deploy Paragon Graphite spyware</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>WhatsApp fixed a zero-click, zero-day vulnerability exploited to install Paragon’s Graphite spyware on targeted individuals. The company addressed the issue in December without a client-side update and did not disclose the locations of the affected users. Meta discovered and dismantled a malware campaign targeting journalists and civil society members with Paragon's spyware (Graphite).</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://securityaffairs.com/175629/security/whatsapp-fixed-zero-day-flaw-used-to-deploy-paragon-graphite-spyware-spyware.html">Reference</a></p>>
		<p><a href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/whatsapp-patched-zero-day-flaw-used-in-paragon-spyware-attacks/">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/whatsapp-patched-zero-day-flaw-used-in-paragon-spyware-attacks/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>ClearFake’s New Widespread Variant: Increased Web3 Exploitation for Malware Delivery</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>ClearFake is a malicious JavaScript framework that injects fake browser updates into compromised websites through Drive-by Downloads. It uses JavaScript injected into websites to download two additional payloads from the C2 server. The latest variant introduced EtherHiding and used smart contracts from the Binance Smart Chain to obtain the second payload. ClearFake's interactions with the blockchain include fetching a single malicious JavaScript from one Ethereum address, delivering loaders like Amadey, IDAT Loader, and HIjack Loader, and deploying infostealers such as Lumma and Stealc. The developer encrypted ClickFix HTML code and hosted it on Cloudflare Pages to evade detection. ClearFake uses the web3 library to interact with Binance Smart Chain's contracts, including a custom ABI for the contract.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://blog.sekoia.io/clearfakes-new-widespread-variant-increased-web3-exploitation-for-malware-delivery/">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://blog.sekoia.io/clearfakes-new-widespread-variant-increased-web3-exploitation-for-malware-delivery/]]></link>
	</item>	
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Dragon ransomware threat assessment</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Researchers from SentinelOne reported on Dragon RaaS, a ransomware group that straddles the boundary between cyber activism and cybercrime. Also referred to as DragonRansom or Dragon Team, the group emerged in July 2024 as a splinter faction of Stormous, which itself is linked to a broader cybercriminal syndicate known as The Five Families—an alliance that includes ThreatSec, GhostSec, Blackforums, and SiegedSec. Its primary targets include entities in the United States, Israel, the United Kingdom, France, and Germany.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.sentinelone.com/blog/dragon-raas-pro-russian-hacktivist-group-aimsto-build-on-the-five-families-cybercrime-reputation/">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.sentinelone.com/blog/dragon-raas-pro-russian-hacktivist-group-aimsto-build-on-the-five-families-cybercrime-reputation/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Windows Shortcut Exploit ZDI-CAN-25373 abused as zeroday in widespread APT campaigns</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Researchers from Trend Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) have identified nearly 1,000 malicious .lnk files leveraging ZDI-CAN-25373, a vulnerability that allows attackers to execute hidden malicious commands via crafted shortcut files. This flaw has been exploited in cyber espionage and data theft campaigns led by state-sponsored groups from North Korea, Iran, Russia, and China, affecting government, financial, telecommunications, defense, military, and energy sectors across North America, Europe, Asia, South America, and Australia.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>ZDI researchers traced the use of ZDI-CAN-25373 across multiple cyber operations dating back to 2017, uncovering its widespread abuse by at least 11 state-sponsored APT groups. North Korean APT groups were found to be the most active exploiters of this vulnerability, with nearly half of the known state-sponsored attacks attributed to them. These groups demonstrated extensive cross-collaboration in techniques, tools, and infrastructure.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.trendmicro.com/en_us/research/25/c/windows-shortcut-zero-day-exploit.html">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-zero-day-exploited-by-11-state-hacking-groups-since-2017/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>DCRat distribution campaign against defense-industrial base</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>CERT-UA has reportedly observed a series of targeted cyberattacks against employees of Ukraine's defense-industrial complex and members of the Defense Forces. These attacks, tracked as UAC-0200, have been ongoing since mid-2024 and escalated in early 2025.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>In March 2025, Signal Messenger was identified as a distribution channel for malicious archived messages, often disguised as meeting reports. To enhance credibility, attackers used previously compromised contacts to send messages. The archives typically included a PDF file along with DarkTortilla, a cryptor/loader designed to decrypt and execute Dark Crystal RAT (DCRAT) for remote control of infected systems.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cert.gov.ua/article/6282737]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hackers Exploit ChatGPT with CVE-2024-27564, 10,000+ Attacks in a Week</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In its latest research report, cybersecurity firm Veriti has spotted active exploitation of a vulnerability within “OpenAI’s ChatGPT infrastructure” but there is no evidence that OpenAI itself has been breached.
		This attack has a global impact, with the United States experiencing the highest concentration of attacks at 33%, followed by Germany and Thailand, each at 7%. Other affected regions include Indonesia, Colombia, and the United Kingdom.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://hackread.com/hackers-exploit-chatgpt-cve-2024-27564-10000-attacks/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Sneaky 2FA, a phishing tool marketed through Telegram</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Sneaky 2FA, believed to be sold via the phishing-as-a-service (PhaaS) business model, recently figured in an adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) attack targeting Microsoft 365 users. Marketed as Sneaky Log by a full-featured bot on Telegram, Sneaky 2FA reportedly used fake Microsoft authentication pages with automatically filled-in email address fields to add to its sense of authenticity.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://circleid.com/posts/sneaking-a-peek-into-the-inner-dns-workings-of-sneaky-2fa]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Targeted OAuth redirection attacks exploit Microsoft 365 for credential theft and malware delivery</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Threat researchers at Proofpoint have detected two ongoing, highly targeted cyber campaigns that exploit OAuth redirection mechanisms in combination with brand impersonation. These campaigns are designed to facilitate Microsoft 365-themed credential phishing and distribute malware, ultimately leading to account takeovers (ATO).
		The campaigns highlight growing risks associated with OAuth-based attacks, which leverage legitimate authentication mechanisms to deceive users and gain unauthorized access.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://x.com/threatinsight/status/1899869276053635553">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-adobe-docusign-oauth-apps-target-microsoft-365-accounts/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Babuk ransomware group claimed to have hacked the French telecommunications company Orange</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On 16 March 2025, Babuk ransomware claimed responsibility for a cyberattack against Orange, a French multinational telecommunications company. The threat actor alleges to have exfiltrated 4.5 terabytes of sensitive data, including customer records, employee information, internal documents, and financial data. If verified, this breach could pose significant risks to Orange customers and employees. Cybernews researchers consider the claims credible based on a provided data sample.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://dnsc.ro/citeste/precizari-cu-privire-la-informatii-aparute-public-despre-un-potential-nou-atac-cibernetic-asupra-companiei-orange">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cybernews.com/security/hackers-threaten-release-of-orange-clients-data/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cybercriminals Exploit CSS to Bypass Spam Filters and Track Users</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cisco Talos researchers identified a new technique used by cybercriminals to bypass spam filters and track user behavior via email. Malicious actors are exploiting Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) properties to hide content from detection engines and fingerprint recipients' email clients. This method allows attackers to evade security measures and potentially direct users to phishing sites.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thehackernews.com/2025/03/cybercriminals-exploit-css-to-evade.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Microsoft Discovers StilachiRAT: A Sophisticated Remote Access Trojan</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft has identified a new remote access trojan (RAT), dubbed StilachiRAT, that employs sophisticated evasion, persistence, and data exfiltration techniques. The malware can steal credentials, monitor clipboard activity, clone security tokens, and hijack active RDP sessions. Though its distribution remains limited, Microsoft has issued indicators of compromise (IOCs) and mitigation guidance to assist defenders.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-new-rat-malware-used-for-crypto-theft-reconnaissance/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>CISA Rehires Fired Employees, Immediately Puts Them on Leave</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>CISA rehires fired employees immediately on administrative leave pending a court decision. The agency plans to place them on immediate leave pending the outcome of a federal judge's ruling. The agency is charged with protecting U.S. federal networks, but has been forced to remove 130 employees amid Trump and Musk's push for workforce cuts.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bankinfosecurity.com/cisa-rehires-fired-employees-immediately-puts-them-on-leave-a-27743]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Third of UK Supply Chain Relies on “Chinese Military” Companies</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>UK companies with larger, complex digital supply chains are heavily reliant on firms linked to the Chinese military, while a study by Bitsight found that 29.1 different providers and 81.6 different products amount to a 10% larger attack surface for threat actors. Providers of digital products are often more exposed to security risks than their customers due to complex vendor relationships and larger attack surfaces.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/news/third-uk-supply-chain-relies/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Alleged Data Breach at Korea Aerospace Research Institute Sparks Major Investigation</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The investigation into a suspected breach of South Korea's Nuri space launch vehicle project involves an employee named A, who is under scrutiny for violating unfair competition laws. Colleague B, who resigned and joined a private company, has also been investigated. Evidence suggests that A and B exchanged sensitive data via messenger.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://databreaches.net/2025/03/18/alleged-data-breach-at-korea-aerospace-research-institute-sparks-major-investigation/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Chinese Hackers Target European Diplomats with Malware</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Chinese hackers targeted European diplomats with malware, and MirrorFace expanded its operations to target a European organization with a refreshed set of hacking tools. Researchers from Eset spotted the hacking group tracked as MirrorFace and Earth Kasha deploying a backdoor previously exclusively used by APT10. The backdoor is known as Anel, also tracked as Uppercut. MirrorFace's use of the backdoor caused Eset to reclassify the group as a subgroup of APT10. Researchers observed the group running a heavily customized AsyncRAT inside Windows Sandbox and abusing Visual Studio Code's remote tunnels for stealthy access.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bankinfosecurity.com/chinese-hackers-target-european-diplomats-malware-a-27745]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>British law requires platforms to take measures against illegal content</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Online platforms in the United Kingdom should take measures to prevent users from being confronted with illegal content and must remove it as soon as possible if exposed. They are required to assess their risk analysis before 16 March and implement concrete measures or have a plan. Offcom advises them to assess file sharing services for CSAM and write management programmes to prevent the spread of CSAM fathers through their services.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.security.nl/posting/880178/Britse+wet+verplicht+platforms+tot+maatregelen+tegen+illegale+content]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>European Cyber Report 2025: 137% more DDoS attacks than last year </h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cyberattacks are now a significant risk for companies worldwide, with an alarming trend of increased DDoS attacks and shorter, more targeted, and more technically sophisticated attacks. Organizations that do not continuously evolve their security strategies face significant financial losses and long-term reputational damage. The Allianz Risk Barometer 2025 highlights the growing limitations of traditional DDoS defenses, emphasizing the need for more adaptive mitigation strategies. Link11 is a specialized global IT security provider that protects infrastructures and web applications from cyberattacks.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://latesthackingnews.com/2025/03/17/european-cyber-report-2025-137-more-ddos-attacks-than-last-year-what-companies-need-to-know/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Popular GitHub Action Targeted in Supply Chain Attack</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A popular GitHub Action called `tj-actions/changed-files` has been compromised in a supply chain attack targeting secrets associated with CI/CD. The incident started on March 14 and involved a threat actor modifying the code to execute a malicious Python script designed to dump CI/CD (continuous integration and continuous delivery) secrets to build logs. StepSecurity, a security company specializing in GitHub Actions, found no evidence of leaked secrets being exfiltrated. Software supply chain security firm Endor Labs has also tracked this incident and found no evidence that downstream open source libraries or containers have been impacted.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.securityweek.com/popular-github-action-targeted-in-supply-chain-attack/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hackers are exploiting Fortinet firewall bugs to plant ransomware</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Security researchers have identified a group called "Mora_001" that exploits Fortinet firewall vulnerabilities to deploy a custom ransomware strain called "SuperBlack." The Mora_001 threat actor exhibits a distinct operational signature, which the firm claims has close ties to the LockBit ransomware gang. Hostetler from Arctic Wolf notes that Forescout's findings suggest hackers are targeting remaining organizations who were unable to apply the patch or harden their firewall configurations when the vulnerability was originally disclosed.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://techcrunch.com/2025/03/17/hackers-are-exploiting-fortinet-firewall-bugs-to-plant-ransomware/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Chinese Chatbot DeepSeek used to develop keylogger and ransomware with little review</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Tenable researchers found that Chinese Chatbot DeepSeek could develop keylogger and ransomware without review. The chatbot refused to write code for these purposes, insisting on using human assistance instead.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.redhotcyber.com/post/chatbot-cinese-deepseek-usato-per-sviluppare-keylogger-e-ransomware-con-poca-review/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>US leads global online fraud rates</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A study by ZeroBounce identified the United States as the country most impacted by online fraud with a high risk score of 64.2%. The US has the highest fraud rate at 0.3% and incidents occur mostly online, with 83% happening through digital channels. France follows closely behind with a risk score of 54.8%, followed by the UK (risk score of 50.2%), Ireland (risk score of 41.2%), Denmark (risk score of 34.1), Luxembourg (risk score of 30.7), Austria (risk score of 26.0), Netherlands (risk score of 25.3), and the UK (risk score of 28.1%).</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://ecommercenews.asia/story/us-leads-global-online-fraud-rates-new-study-reveals]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Head Mare and Twelve reportedly collaborating to attack Russian entities</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Analysts from Kaspersky identified a series of cyberattacks targeting Russian companies in September 2024, revealing a strong correlation between two hacktivist groups, Head Mare and Twelve (alias -=TWELVE=-). Analysis identified shared infrastructure, malware, and tactics between the two groups, suggesting a potential collaboration in their campaigns.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Formed in April 2023, Twelve historically targeted Russian entities. The group reportedly went silent for several months, but on mid-2024, the group appeared to have re-emerged. Head Mare is believed to be a hacktivist group that historically targeted Russian and Russia-aligned organizations, active since at least the end of 2023.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securelist.com/head-mare-twelve-collaboration/115887/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Phishing campaign impersonates Booking .com, delivers a suite of credential-stealing malware</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Starting in December 2024, leading up to some of the busiest travel days, Microsoft Threat Intelligence identified a phishing campaign that impersonates online travel agency Booking.com and targets organizations in the hospitality industry. The campaign uses a social engineering technique called ClickFix to deliver multiple credential-stealing malware in order to conduct financial fraud and theft. As of February 2025, this campaign is ongoing.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>This phishing attack specifically targets individuals in hospitality organizations in North America, Oceania, South and Southeast Asia, and Northern, Southern, Eastern, and Western Europe, that are most likely to work with Booking.com, sending fake emails purporting to be coming from the agency.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/security/blog/2025/03/13/phishing-campaign-impersonates-booking-com-delivers-a-suite-of-credential-stealing-malware/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Europe's telecoms sector under increased threat from cyber spies, warns Denmark</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Denmark’s cybersecurity agency published a threat assessment on Thursday warning of an increase in state-sponsored cyber espionage activities targeting the telecommunications sector in Europe.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>It is the first public warning by a European government agency that suggests governments on the continent share the alarm of the United States over a Chinese spying campaign tracked as Salt Typhoon, although the Danish authorities did not explicitly mention Salt Typhoon or China.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://therecord.media/europe-increased-cyber-espionage-telecoms-denmark-report]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Signal No Longer Cooperating with Ukraine to Tackle Russian Cyber Threats</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The encrypted messaging app Signal has ceased responding to Ukrainian law enforcement requests regarding Russian cyber threats, a senior Ukrainian official claimed, warning that this inaction is aiding Moscow’s intelligence operations.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>According to Serhii  Demediuk (deputy secretary of Ukraine’s National Security and Defense Council), Ukraine had previously communicated with Signal through an official channel to warn about the app’s abuse by Russian hackers. These attacks reportedly involve phishing campaigns and account takeovers, often targeting Ukrainian military and government personnel. While Signal previously responded to such concerns, Demediuk said this is no longer the case.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cyberinsider.com/signal-no-longer-cooperating-with-ukraine-to-tackle-russian-cyber-threats/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Over 400 IPs exploiting multiple SSRF vulnerabilities in coordinated cyberattack</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On March 9, 2025, GreyNoise started to observe a coordinated surge in Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)  exploitation, with over 400 unique IP addresses actively targeting multiple SSRF vulnerabilities across various platforms. The United States, Germany, Singapore, India, Lithuania, Israel and Japan have been identified as the top countries experiencing SSRF exploitation attempts</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>ENISA has issued a Flash Report on the subject on 13.03.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.greynoise.io/blog/new-ssrf-exploitation-surge">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thehackernews.com/2025/03/over-400-ips-exploiting-multiple-ssrf.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>A new Android spyware named 'KoSpy' is linked to North Korean threat actors who have infiltrated Google Play</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A new Android spyware named 'KoSpy' is linked to North Korean threat actors who have infiltrated Google Play and third-party app store APKPure through at least five malicious apps.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The spyware campaign primarily targets Korean and English-speaking users by disguising itself as file managers, security tools, and software updaters. The campaign was attributed to APT37.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.lookout.com/threat-intelligence/article/lookout-discovers-new-spyware-by-north-korean-apt37">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-north-korean-android-spyware-slips-onto-google-play/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cybersecurity firm Dragos has revealed a prolonged cyberattack by the Chinese threat actor Volt Typhoon into the United States electric grid</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>State-sponsored Volt Typhoon hackers were poking around the Littleton Electric Light and Water Departments for at least 300 days before the FBI gave the utility a heads up. Dragos released a case study about the hack, which it blamed on Voltzite, a "sophisticated threat group...that overlaps with Volt Typhoon."</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://hackread.com/chinese-volt-typhoon-hackers-infiltrated-us-electric-grid/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.dragos.com/resources/case-study/hunting-active-threats-littleton-grid-with-dragos-platform-ot-watch/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>China-linked cyberespionage actor UNC3886 targets Juniper routers</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On March 12, Mandiant reported that China-nexus group UNC3886 exploited Juniper Networks routers between mid-2023 and early 2024. The attackers deployed custom backdoors with active and passive capabilities, allowing long-term access while disabling logging mechanisms. This tactic enables persistent espionage and potential future disruptions to critical infrastructure.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/threat-intelligence/china-nexus-espionage-targets-juniper-routers?hl=en]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securityaffairs.com/175308/apt/china-linked-apt-unc3886-targets-eol-juniper-routers.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Alleged TurkNet Data Breach Exposes 2.8 Million Records"></h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>According to the post from DarkWebInformer, the compromised data includes user credentials, email addresses, and potentially financial information. TuirkNet didn't confirm the breach until the time of writing.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cyberpress.org/turknet-data-breach/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Sabotage, espionage, cyberattacks: Russia recruits Belgians and pays them in cryptocurrency</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A VRT NWS investigative report reveals that pro-Russian groups are recruiting Belgians online to conduct espionage, spread disinformation, and carry out cyberattacks, often paying them in cryptocurrency. A journalist infiltrated a Telegram group of over 8,000 members, which had previously disrupted Belgian municipal and government websites. Assigned small propaganda and intelligence-gathering tasks, the journalist was offered cryptocurrency as a reward. The Belgian State Security warns of increasing use of "disposable agents," a tactic also observed in other NATO countries. The investigation was conducted in collaboration with multiple European media outlets.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.sudinfo.be/id966052/article/2025-03-12/sabotage-espionnage-cyberattaques-la-russie-recrute-des-belges-et-les-paye-en]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>[NEW victims identified] Salt Typhoon performs reconnaissance of telecom networks and government infrastructure</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Between December 2024 and February 2025, security analysts identified new activity by the Chinese state-sponsored group Salt Typhoon targeting Cisco network devices worldwide for initial access. Investigations revealed Salt Typhoon’s infrastructure conducting reconnaissance on networks belonging  to the Australian telecommunications provider Spirit Telecom and Myanmar’s MyTel, on mid-February 2025. The group was observed interacting with at least two MyTel devices running Wowza Streaming Engine Manager.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[Leonardo Global CyberSec Center]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>BADBOX 2.0, a complex, China-based operation that compromised off-brand devices</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>BADBOX 2.0 is an expanded and more sophisticated version of a China-based cyber operation that compromised over a million off-brand Android-powered devices, including TVs, smartphones, tablets, and car infotainment systems. Discovered by HUMAN’s Satori Threat Intelligence team, this botnet facilitated various fraud schemes such as ad fraud, credential theft, and DDoS attacks, often without users noticing. The malware came pre-installed on some devices, while others were infected through unofficial app downloads. Researchers suspect multiple threat actor groups collaborated in the operation.</p>]]> 
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.humansecurity.com/learn/blog/badbox-2-0-the-sequel-no-one-wanted/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>CISA worker says 100-strong red team fired after DOGE cancelled contract</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A penetration tester who worked at the US govt's CISA claims his 100-strong team was dismissed after Elon Musk's Trump-blessed DOGE unit cancelled a contract – and that more staff at the cybersecurity agency have also been let go. "DOGE cut our entire red team and all support roles — over 100 people impacted. The following Wednesday, DOGE cut a second CISA red team also doing mission-critical work. As a result, I and many other experienced red team operators are now seeking new opportunities."</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theregister.com/2025/03/12/cisa_staff_layoffs/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Microsoft quantum breakthrough claims labelled 'unreliable' and 'essentially fraudulent'</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft's claim of having made quantum computing breakthroughs has attracted strong criticism from scientists, but the software giant says it’s work is sound – and it will soon reveal data that proves it. The quantum claims were made in February when Microsoft announced its in-house boffins had created "the world’s first topoconductor, a breakthrough type of material which can observe and control Majorana particles to produce more reliable and scalable qubits, which are the building blocks for quantum computers."</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theregister.com/2025/03/12/microsoft_majorana_quantum_claims_overshadowed/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>X hit by massive cyberattack amid Dark Storm’s DDoS claims</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Dark Storm hacktivist group claims to be behind DDoS attacks causing multiple X worldwide outages on Monday, leading the company to enable DDoS protections from Cloudflare.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>While X owner Elon Musk did not specifically state that DDoS attacks were behind the outages, he did confirm that it was caused by a "massive cyberattack."</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/x-hit-by-massive-cyberattack-amid-dark-storms-ddos-claims/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Researchers expose new polymorphic attack that clones browser extensions to steal credentials</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cybersecurity researchers have demonstrated a novel technique that allows a malicious web browser extension to impersonate any installed add-on. The harvested credentials could then be abused by the threat actors to hijack online accounts and gain unauthorized access to sensitive personal and financial information. The attack affects all Chromium-based web browsers, including Google Chrome, Microsoft Edge, Brave, Opera, and others.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://labs.sqrx.com/polymorphic-extensions-dd2310006e04">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thehackernews.com/2025/03/researchers-expose-new-polymorphic.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>SideWinder APT Targets Maritime, Nuclear, and IT Sectors Across Asia, Middle East, and Africa</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Maritime and logistics companies in South and Southeast Asia, the Middle East, and Africa have become the target of an advanced persistent threat (APT) group dubbed SideWinder.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The attacks, observed by Kaspersky in 2024, spread across Bangladesh, Cambodia, Djibouti, Egypt, the United Arab Emirates, and Vietnam. Other targets of interest include nuclear power plants and nuclear energy infrastructure in South Asia and Africa, as well as telecommunication, consulting, IT service companies, real estate agencies, and hotels.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thehackernews.com/2025/03/sidewinder-apt-targets-maritime-nuclear.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>ANSSI's cybercrime report 2024</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In line with previous years, ANSSI now estimates that attackers linked to the cybercriminal ecosystem or known to be linked to China and Russia constitute the three main threats to both the most critical information systems (IS) and the national ecosystem in a systemic manner.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cyber.gouv.fr/publications/panorama-de-la-cybermenace-2024]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Z-Pentest Alliance claimed to have unauthorized access to the water supply infrastructure in the Valencian Community of Spain</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>NoName057(16) has claimed responsibility for unauthorized access to the water supply infrastructure in the Valencian Community of Spain. The threat actor published these claims on their Telegram channel and included a video related to their alleged cyber attack.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://dailydarkweb.net/noname05716targets-water-supply-system-in-spain/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Ministry of Internal Affairs Hospital in Krakow became the target of a cyberattack</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>According to the Vice PM, cybersecurity agencies, including Poland’s Cyberspace Emergency Response Team (CERT Polska), e-Health Center, and Central Bureau for Combating Cybercrime, are gathering evidence and helping the healthcare facility resume normal operations. Law enforcers have coordinated efforts to identify the perpetrators of the attack.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.ukrinform.net/rubric-society/3968608-police-hospital-in-poland-targeted-in-cyberattack.html">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://dorzeczy.pl/kraj/700629/cyberatak-na-szpital-mswia-w-krakowie-komunikat-z-rzadu.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Magic Hound registers new infrastructure tied to Arda PowerLess malware</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Security researchers identified new infrastructure linked to the Iranian statesponsored threat group Magic Hound, registered between January and mid-February 2025. This infrastructure is highly likely connected to a cluster previously reported by Recorded Future in December 2024, which was associated with the PowerLess malware variant “Arda”. While this infrastructure appears to function as both command-and-control (C2) and malware dissemination for Magic Hound activity, no new malware samples have been identified at this time.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[Leonardo Global CyberSec Center]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>North Korean hackers cash out hundreds of millions from $1.5bn ByBit hack</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Hackers thought to be working for the North Korean regime have successfully converted at least $300m (£232m) of their record-breaking $1.5bn crypto heist to unrecoverable funds. The criminals, known as Lazarus Group, swiped the huge haul of digital tokens in a hack on crypto exchange ByBit two weeks ago.</p> 
		<p></p>
		<p>Since then, it's been a cat-and-mouse game to track and block the hackers from successfully converting the crypto into usable cash. Experts say the infamous hacking team is working nearly 24 hours a day - potentially funnelling the money into the regime's military development.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c2kgndwwd7lo]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Large-scale cryptocurrency miner campaign targets Russian users with SilentCryptoMiner</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Kaspersky researchers discovered a mass malware campaign spreading SilentCryptoMiner by disguising it as a tool to bypass internet restrictions. While investigating the increased use of Windows Packet Divert (WPD) tools by crooks to distribute malware under this pretense, the researchers spotted the campaign.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.kaspersky.com/blog/miner-disguised-as-circumvention-tools/53118/">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securityaffairs.com/175169/breaking-news/miner-campaign-targeting-russian-users-with-silentcryptominer.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Reporting cyberattacks on critical infrastructure mandatory from 1 April</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>At its meeting on 7 March, the Swiss Federal Council introduced a reporting obligation for cyberattacks on critical infrastructure, which will come into force on 1 April. Operators of critical infrastructure will be required to report cyberattacks to the National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) within 24 hours of discovery. These reports will enable the NCSC to assist victims of cyberattacks and alert operators of critical infrastructure.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.admin.ch/gov/en/start/documentation/media-releases.msg-id-104400.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Vulnerable ESXi Servers exploited all over EU</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>2,800 Vulnerable VMware ESXi Servers in Germany Exploited.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Over 900 VMware ESXi Servers in Netherlands Affected by Critical Vulnerability</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.security.nl/posting/878852/%2737_000+VMware+ESXi-servers+missen+update+voor+actief+aangevallen+lek%27?channel=rss">Reference</a></p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.heise.de/news/Attacken-auf-VMware-ESXi-Immer-noch-zehntausende-Server-verwundbar-10307632.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Microsoft says malvertising campaign impacted 1 million PCs</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In early December 2024, Microsoft Threat Intelligence detected a large-scale malvertising campaign that impacted nearly one million devices globally in an opportunistic attack to steal information. The attack originated from illegal streaming websites embedded with malvertising redirectors, leading to an intermediary website where the user was then redirected to GitHub and two other platforms. The campaign impacted a wide range of organizations and industries, including both consumer and enterprise devices, highlighting the indiscriminate nature of the attack.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/security/blog/2025/03/06/malvertising-campaign-leads-to-info-stealers-hosted-on-github/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Data breach at Japanese telecom giant NTT hits 18,000 companies</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Japanese telecommunication services provider NTT Communications Corporation (NTT) is warning almost 18,000 corporate customers that their information was compromised during a cybersecurity incident.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/data-breach-at-japanese-telecom-giant-ntt-hits-18-000-companies/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>EU ministers sign cybersecurity declaration in Warsaw</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>During the meeting, participants agreed that investing in Europe’s digital resilience must go hand in hand with establishing more effective coordination and incident response mechanisms at the EU level. To reaffirm their commitment to closer cooperation on cybersecurity, Council members unanimously adopted the Warsaw Call declaration.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://polish-presidency.consilium.europa.eu/en/news/warsaw-call-declaration-adopted-at-the-informal-tte-telecom-council-on-cybersecurity/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>ENISA NIS360 report</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The NIS360 is a new ENISA product that assesses the maturity and criticality of sectors of high criticality under the NIS2 Directive, providing both a comparative overview and a more in-depth analysis of each sector. The NIS360 is designed to assist Member States and national authorities in identifying gaps and prioritising resources. Our analysis is based on data from national authorities with a horizontal or sectorial mandate, data from companies within the in-scope sectors, and insights from EU-level sources such as Eurostat.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.enisa.europa.eu/publications/enisa-nis360-2024]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cyber-attack on flight tracking portal</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Flightradar24 is a Swedish Internet-based service that shows real-time aircraft flight tracking information on a map. It includes flight tracking information, origins and destinations, flight numbers, aircraft types, positions, altitudes, headings and speeds.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.dmm.travel/nc/news/cyber-angriff-auf-flugverfolgungsportal]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Typosquatted Go packages delivering malware loader targeting Linux and macOS systems</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Security researchers at Socket have identified an ongoing malware campaign infiltrating the Go ecosystem using typosquatted packages. The campaign introduces malicious loader malware targeting Linux and macOS systems, with at least 7 fraudulent packages impersonating widely used Go libraries. One of these packages appears to specifically target developers in the financial sector.</p> 
		<p></p>
		<p>The malicious packages have been found using consistent obfuscation techniques and repeated filenames, indicating a well-organized threat actor capable of rapidly adjusting their tactics. These packages remain available on the Go Module Mirror, and Socket has requested their removal while reporting the associated GitHub repositories and user accounts.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://socket.dev/blog/typosquatted-go-packages-deliver-malware-loader]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>FOG ransomware group has leaked source code of 19 new victims</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Fog ransomware has leaked the source code of 19 new victims, many of them located in the EU. Also included EUMETSTAT, Europe's meteorological satellite agency, based in Darmstadt, Germany.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://x.com/FalconFeedsio/status/1897443186198634692]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>US charges 12 Chinese hackers in major government-backed espionage campaign</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>US authorities have announced criminal charges against 12 Chinese nationals allegedly involved in a long-running cyber-espionage campaign tied to China’s government.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>According to court documents, among those charged are two officers from China’s Ministry of Public Security (MPS), while the remaining ten worked for Anxun Information Technology, commonly known as i-Soon, a private firm allegedly connected to China’s APT27 hacking group, also called Silk Typhoon.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.csoonline.com/article/3840168/us-charges-12-chinese-hackers-in-major-government-backed-espionage-campaign.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Over Half of Organizations Report Serious OT Security Incidents</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>More than half of global organizations have suffered an operational technology (OT) incident over the past 12 months, according to the SANS Institute. A particular concern is that “IT compromise” (58%) was cited as the most common OT attack vector, indicating the converged nature of the two historically siloed functions. Yet despite this, only 27% of budget decisions are led by CISOs.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://osintcorp.net/over-half-of-organizations-report-serious-ot-security-incidents/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russian telecom Beeline facing disruptions after cyberattack</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cybersecurity media outlet The Record informs that the Russian telecommunications company Beeline faced a Distributed-Denial-of-Service (DDoS) that disrupted internet services for many users in Russia. Beeline, which serves over 44 million subscribers, confirmed the incident following reports from outage-tracking platforms and customer complaints. According to Downdetector, most disruptions affected Beeline’s mobile application, while some users also experienced website outages, notification failures, and general internet connectivity issues.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://therecord.media/russian-telecom-beeline-outages-cyber]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>North Korean Fake IT Workers Pose as Blockchain Developers on GitHub</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A network of North Korean fake IT workers has been creating personas on GitHub to obtain remote engineering and full-stack blockchain developer positions in the US and Japan, threat monitoring firm Nisos warns. The GitHub personas, which are reusing matured GitHub accounts and portfolio content, claim to be in Asia, and some of them appear to be employed at small companies.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.securityweek.com/north-korean-fake-it-workers-pose-as-blockchain-developers-on-github/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hackers exploiting vulnerabilities faster than organizations can patch</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A cybersecurity firm's latest threat landscape report highlights an increasing urgency for organizations to strengthen their defenses. Hackers are now exploiting new vulnerabilities almost immediately, outpacing the time it takes most businesses to apply security patches. The report also points to a significant rise in IoT attacks, while other threats like malware and cryptojacking have seen some decline. Business email compromise has become a dominant cyber threat, with a sharp increase in incidents, particularly targeting corporate users. In healthcare, ransomware remains the most pressing issue, driving nearly all major breaches. Additionally, attackers are leveraging AI and more precise targeting strategies to exploit small- and medium-sized enterprises.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cybersecasia.net/newsletter/hackers-exploiting-vulnerabilities-faster-than-organizations-can-patch/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Silk Typhoon targeting IT supply chain</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft Threat Intelligence identified a shift in tactics by Silk Typhoon, a Chinese espionage group, now targeting common IT solutions like remote management tools and cloud applications to gain initial access. While they haven’t been observed directly targeting Microsoft cloud services, they do exploit unpatched applications that allow them to elevate their access in targeted organizations and conduct further malicious activities. After successfully compromising a victim, Silk Typhoon uses the stolen keys and credentials to infiltrate customer networks where they can then abuse a variety of deployed applications, including Microsoft services and others, to achieve their espionage objectives. Our latest blog explains how Microsoft security solutions detect these threats and offers mitigation guidance, aiming to raise awareness and strengthen defenses against Silk Typhoon’s activities.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/security/blog/2025/03/05/silk-typhoon-targeting-it-supply-chain/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Outage of Dutch government authentication system DigiD</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On 3 March 2025, a series of distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks caused an outage of DigiD, the Netherlands' government authentication system. The attack reportedly affected several digital government services as it was not possible to log in to several websites where DigiD is used as an authentication method. These include, for example, municipal government websites, health insurers, pension funds and the Tax and Customs Administration. MijnOverheid, the platform for citizens to access government correspondence and personal records, was also impacted by the outage.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://nltimes.nl/2025/03/03/cyberattack-hits-dutch-government-login-digid-blocking-access-many-services">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.nu.nl/tech/6347833/storing-bij-digid-opgelost-inloggen-op-overheidswebsites-weer-mogelijk.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Nearly 12.000 API keys and passwords exposed in AI training dataset</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 27, researchers at Truffle Security, the company behind the TruffleHog open-source scanner for sensitive data, discovered nearly 12.000 valid API keys and passwords in the Common Crawl dataset, which is used to train various AI models. The exposed secrets included AWS and MailChimp API keys, raising concerns about insecure coding practices influencing AI behaviour despite pre-processing efforts to remove sensitive information.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://trufflesecurity.com/blog/research-finds-12-000-live-api-keys-and-passwords-in-deepseek-s-training-data]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>	
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>A newly discovered ClickFix phishing campaign deploys Havoc C2 via Microsoft Sharepoint</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A newly uncovered ClickFix phishing campaign is tricking victims into executing malicious PowerShell commands that deploy the Havok post-exploitation framework for remote access. Discovered by Fortinet’s FortiGuard Labs, the campaign delivers phishing emails with fake OneDrive error messages, urging users to run a copied PowerShell command. This command downloads a secondary script from a SharePoint server, which checks for sandbox environments, installs Python if needed, and then deploys Havok as an injected DLL. The malware communicates through Microsoft’s Graph API, disguising malicious activity within legitimate cloud traffic. ClickFix attacks are growing in popularity, with cybercriminals using similar tactics across phishing emails and social media platforms to spread various malware strains.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-clickfix-attack-deploys-havoc-c2-via-microsoft-sharepoint/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Suspected Iranian Hackers Used Compromised Indian Firm's Email to Target U.A.E. Aviation Sector</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A newly discovered phishing campaign, attributed to an emerging group tracked as UNK_CraftyCamel, has targeted fewer than five aviation and satellite communications entities in the UAE using a previously undocumented Golang backdoor called Sosano. Detected in October 2024 by Proofpoint, the attack exploited a compromised email account from the Indian company INDIC Electronics to send phishing emails with malicious ZIP attachments. These contained polyglot files and disguised shortcuts to execute Sosano, which enables attackers to execute shell commands, manipulate directories, and download additional payloads. Researchers suspect Iranian-aligned actors, possibly linked to the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC), given the campaign's strategic focus on critical infrastructure.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thehackernews.com/2025/03/suspected-iranian-hackers-used.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Massive GitHub Malware Campaign Targets Gamers and Software Pirates with Redox Stealer</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A newly discovered malware campaign is exploiting GitHub to distribute Redox Stealer, an information-stealing malware targeting gamers, software pirates, and modding enthusiasts. Cybercriminals have created thousands of fake repositories offering mods, game cheats, and cracked software for popular titles like Roblox, Fortnite, and Photoshop. Once downloaded and executed, Redox Stealer silently collects sensitive data, including banking credentials, cryptocurrency wallets, and gaming accounts, exfiltrating it to Discord servers for cybercriminals to exploit. Attackers use SEO poisoning, AI-generated content, and obfuscation techniques to evade detection, overwhelming GitHub’s security measures as new repositories are continuously created and re-uploaded.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securityonline.info/massive-github-malware-campaign-targets-gamers-and-software-pirates-with-redox-stealer/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>3 March, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>USA - Russia cyber relations</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 28, The Record reported that Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth ordered US Cyber Command to halt all planning against Russia, including offensive cyber operations. This directive, issued to Cyber Command chief General Timothy Haugh, does not affect the National Security Agency's intelligence activities targeting Russia. The move aligns with the administration's efforts to normalise relations with Moscow.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>On February 28, The Guardian reported that the Trump administration is downplaying Russia's cyber threat, diverging from longstanding intelligence assessments. This shift was evident when State Department official Liesyl Franz named China and Iran as cyber threats but omitted Russia. Additionally, the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has reportedly been directed to deprioritise reporting on Russian cyber threats.	</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://therecord.media/hegseth-orders-cyber-command-stand-down-russia-planning]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/feb/28/trump-russia-hacking-cyber-security]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>CERT-EU Cyber brief - February 2025</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In the brief  the reader will find the analysis based on 433 Open Source reports. </p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Policy, cooperation, and law enforcement. The EU aims to strengthen the EU's response to large-scale cyber incidents, Sweden and the UK seek backdoor access to private companies, and a former Polish Justice Minister arrested in Pegasus spyware case. Moreover, the US stands down on cyber Russia planning, Japan approves Cyber Defence Bill to counter sophisticated threats, Australian government bans Kaspersky products from government systems, and several police operations result in the arrest of cybercriminals.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Cyberespionage. China-linked threat actors compromised Belgian Secret Service e-mail exchanges, as well as telecommunications worldwide. Russia-linked threat actor Sandworm was active in targeting critical infrastructure in Europe. Multiple Russian threat actors targeted Microsoft device code authentication and Signal Messenger in multiple sectors, including defence. Pegasus software infected at least one EU government official, while another Israeli spyware targeted EU civil society, and North Korea continues targeting developers.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Cybercrime. The Belgian Port of Ostend was a victim of a cyberattack, China-linked threat actors were active in cybercrime worldwide, as were North Korea-linked Lazarus group, who namely carried out what is considered the largest cryptocurrency theft in history.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Information operations. China-linked Spamouflage operation targets the Spanish government, and a report analysed the impact of AI-driven disinformation in financial destabilisation. OpenAI removed accounts from China and North Korea that misused ChatGPT for malicious activities.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Data exposure and leaks. Orange group was a victim of a hack-and-leak attack in Romania, as was the Bulgarian Supreme Administrative Court.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cert.europa.eu/publications/threat-intelligence/cb25-03/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cybersecurity incident at Polish Space Agency (POLSA)</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>According to the official Twitter account, there has been a cybersecurity incident at POLSA. The relevant services and institutions have been informed. The situation is being analyzed. In order to secure data after the hack, the POLSA network was immediately disconnected from the Internet. We will keep you updated.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://x.com/polsa_gov_pl/status/1896247268069765211?s=46&amp;t=u19CbogN0TP7iqFc4MlyEQ]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Vodafone Trials Quantum-Safe Tech to Protect Smartphone Browsing</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Vodafone is trialing new quantum-safe technology using IBM Quantum Safe solutions to protect smartphone users from future quantum-enabled cyber threats. The proof of concept, supported by Akamai, will be tested on Vodafone’s Secure Net service, which safeguards users against phishing, malware, and identity theft. The initiative integrates post-quantum cryptography (PQC) standards to strengthen encryption, addressing concerns that quantum computing could eventually break current cryptographic protections. Vodafone and IBM, both founding members of the GSMA Post-Quantum Telco Network Taskforce, aim to establish a roadmap for implementing quantum-safe security across the telecom industry.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://osintcorp.net/vodafone-trials-quantum-safe-tech-to-protect-smartphone-browsing/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 March, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Palo Alto Networks provides AI-powered security to 5G enterprise customers</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Palo Alto Networks has introduced Prisma SASE 5G, a cloud-native zero trust security solution designed to protect enterprise 5G networks from evolving cyber threats. The platform leverages AI-powered threat detection, SIM-based authentication, and secure access controls to defend against zero-day attacks and malicious malware. To strengthen its private 5G security offerings, Palo Alto Networks has expanded partnerships with industry leaders, including Nokia, NTT DATA, and NVIDIA, integrating its next-generation firewalls with advanced networking and AI solutions. As 5G adoption grows, this initiative aims to provide enterprises with seamless security across IT, OT, and mobile networks, addressing the increasing risks posed by AI-driven cyberattacks.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.helpnetsecurity.com/2025/03/03/palo-alto-networks-prisma-sase-5g/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>China-linked threat actors compromised Belgian Secret Service e-mail exchanges</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 26, the newspaper Le Soir revealed that Chinese threat actors compromised the Belgian Secret Service (VSSE) e-mail exchanges between 2021 and 2023. The threat actors exploited a vulnerability in the e-mail system of a US software supplier, called Barracuda, that was previously reported in 2023 and was being used by Belgian intelligence as well as the Belgian Pipeline Organisation, which monitors pipelines in the North Sea.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>ENISA has issued a Flash Report on this subject on 27 Feb.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.lesoir.be/657866/article/2025-02-26/des-hackers-chinois-ont-vole-des-donnees-sensibles-la-surete-de-letat]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hacktivist group Dark Storm targets ENISA’s website</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 27, 2025, hacktivist group Dark Storm claimed a Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attack targeting ENISA’s website on their Telegram channel. ENISA’s website is up and active and did not suffer service disruption.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://t.me/darkstormchat/1330]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 February, 2025></pubDate>	
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>FBI confirms Lazarus hackers were behind $1.5B Bybit crypto heist</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>FBI has confirmed that North Korean hackers stole $1.5 billion from cryptocurrency exchange Bybit on Friday in the largest crypto heist recorded until now.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The state-sponsored hacking group (tracked as TraderTraitor, Lazarus Group, and APT38) intercepted a scheduled transfer of funds from one of Bybit's cold wallets into a hot wallet, subsequently redirecting the cryptocurrency to a blockchain address under their control.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-confirms-lazarus-hackers-were-behind-15b-bybit-crypto-heist/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>UK Delays Plans for AI Regulation</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The British Labour Government has reportedly delayed plans to put forward a draft bill on artificial intelligence over concerns that binding AI regulation could stifle the country's AI growth potential.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The United Kingdom, like the United States, has so far taken a decentralized approach to AI governance by trusting to existing statutes surrounding data, consumer protection, and product safety to do the work of protecting the populace.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bankinfosecurity.com/uk-delays-plans-for-ai-regulation-a-27596]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>26 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Threat actor leaks Orange Group information from Romania</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 25, a threat actor alleged to have stolen almost 6.5GB of data from Orange Group, specifically from Orange Romania. The leak mainly affects employees, partners, and contractors, as well as some customers. The data contains email addresses, source code, invoices, contracts, customer and employee information. However, according to BleepingComputer who analysed some of the leaked information, most of it seems to be outdated or expired. ENISA has issued a flash report about this incident.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/orange-group-confirms-breach-after-hacker-leaks-company-documents/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>26 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Taiwan detains Togolese-flagged Chinese-crewed cargo ship investigating undersea cable damage</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Taiwan's coastguard has detained a cargo ship along with its Chinese crew following damage to an undersea communications cable in the Taiwan Strait on Tuesday. Officials have not ruled out the possibility that this was a deliberate "grey zone" operation, a term used to describe acts of interference that fall short of open conflict.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cga.gov.tw/GipOpen/wSite/ct?xItem=164475&amp;ctNode=650&amp;=999]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>26 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cyberattack targets Russian IT service provider LANIT Group</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Russia’s National Coordination Center for Computer Incidents (NKTsKI) reported that LANIT, a major Russian IT service provider, experienced a cyberattack on February 21, 2025. The breach affected LANIT’s subsidiaries, LLC LANTER and LLC LAN ATM Service, which specialize in software development for ATMs and payment systems. NKTsKI has not disclosed the initial attack vector, the identity of the threat actor(s), or whether any data was compromised.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://gossopka.ru/pub/nktski-preduprezhdaet-o-komprometatsii-lanit/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>26 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Signal will withdraw from Sweden if encryption-busting laws take effect</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Signal CEO Meredith Whittaker has reaffirmed that the company will exit any country that mandates law enforcement access to encrypted user data, as Sweden considers legislation that could require messaging platforms to implement encryption backdoors by 2026. In an interview with Swedish media, Whittaker emphasized that end-to-end encryption (E2EE) cannot be selectively weakened, stating that any backdoor would compromise security for all users. This stance mirrors Signal’s previous threats to leave the UK over its Online Safety Bill, which included a controversial encryption-breaking clause. Sweden’s proposed law would extend telecom data retention rules to encrypted messaging apps, requiring them to store and decrypt messages for law enforcement—a move critics argue would undermine privacy and cybersecurity.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theregister.com/2025/02/26/signal_will_withdraw_from_sweden/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>26 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Have I Been Pwned Reports Huge Data Leak, Adds 284 Million Stolen Accounts</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cybersecurity service Have I Been Pwned (HIBP) has disclosed one of the largest data exposure events in its 11-year history, integrating 23 billion rows of stolen credentials from a malware operation dubbed “ALIEN TXTBASE.” The breach corpus contains 493 million unique website-email pairs tied to 284 million unique email addresses, alongside 244 million new passwords added to HIBP’s Pwned Passwords database.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://gbhackers.com/have-i-been-pwned-reports-huge-data-leak/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>26 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Ransomware Attacks Focus on Data Exfiltration Over Encryption</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A report by the American cybersecurity firm ReliaQuest reveals that more malware-spreading gangs are targeting data exfiltration. This method is faster, often taking just 48 to 90 minutes, and carries a lower risk of being traced by law enforcement. In contrast, when encryption is used, victims may refuse to comply with ransom demands and contact authorities, complicating the criminals’ plans.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cybersecurity-insiders.com/ransomware-hackers-are-more-interested-in-data-exfiltration-than-encryption/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>25 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>UAC-0212 targeting Ukrainian critical infrastructure and supply chain</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ukrainian Governmental Computer Emergency Response Team (CERT-UA) has reported about an ongoing cyber campaign targeting enterprises in Ukraine’s energy, water, and heating supply sectors. Initially tracked in early 2024 under UAC-0133, the campaign has been attributed with high confidence to UAC-0002, a group associated with Sandworm (APT44, Seashell Blizzard). These operations have evolved in the second half of 2024, incorporating new tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), with attackers leveraging phishing lures and software vulnerabilities to compromise target environments.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cert.gov.ua/article/6282517]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>25 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Apple removes Advanced Data Protection in UK amid government demands</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 21, Apple announced the discontinuation of its Advanced Data Protection (ADP) feature for new users in the UK, with plans to require existing users to disable it in the near future. This decision follows demands from UK security services for backdoor access to encrypted iCloud backups. Despite this change, services such as iMessage, FaceTime, Health data, and iCloud Keychain will continue to have end-to-end encryption in the UK.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theverge.com/news/617273/apple-removes-encryption-advanced-data-protection-adp-uk-spying-backdoor]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>25 February, 2025></pubDate>	
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>OpenAI Purges ChatGPT Accounts: China and North Korea Weaponizing AI for Propaganda</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>OpenAI has confirmed that it is blocking accounts linked to Chinese and North Korean users who were using ChatGPT to monitor and influence social media discourse. These accounts were reportedly tracking anti-China sentiment, enhancing speech-monitoring tools, and generating fabricated news content aimed at tarnishing the U.S. and promoting pro-Beijing narratives, particularly in Latin America. Some were also linked to financial fraud schemes in Cambodia. OpenAI previously identified similar disinformation campaigns involving actors from China, Russia, Iran, and Israel, highlighting growing concerns over AI’s role in online influence operations.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securityonline.info/openai-purges-chatgpt-accounts-china-and-north-korea-weaponizing-ai-for-propaganda/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>25 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Dragos's 8th Annual OT Cybersecurity Year in Review Is Now Available</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 8th Annual OT Cybersecurity Year in Review report from Dragos highlights escalating threats against operational technology (OT) and industrial control systems (ICS). In 2024, industrial ransomware attacks surged by 87%, with adversaries increasingly targeting critical sectors such as energy, manufacturing, and defense. The report introduces two new threat groups, BAUXITE and GRAPHITE, alongside continued activity from groups like VOLTZITE and ELECTRUM. New ICS malware, Fuxnet and FrostyGoop, disrupted infrastructure in Russia and Ukraine, respectively. The findings emphasize persistent security gaps in OT environments, including poor incident response planning, inadequate network segmentation, and insecure remote access. Dragos recommends adopting a risk-based vulnerability management approach and enhancing real-time OT monitoring to counter evolving cyber threats.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.dragos.com/blog/dragos-8th-annual-ot-cybersecurity-year-in-review-is-now-available/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cyber Blueprint - Draft Council Recommendation</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Cyber Blueprint should enable relevant Union-actors (meaning Union-level individual entities and networks of entities) to understand how to interact and make the best use of available mechanisms across the full crisis management lifecycle. It aims to explain what a cyber crisis is and what triggers a cyber crisis mechanism at Union level. It explains the use of available mechanisms like the Cybersecurity Emergency Mechanism, including the EU Cybersecurity Reserve, in preparing how to manage, respond to and recover from a crisis arising from a large-scale cybersecurity incident. It furthermore aims to foster a more structured cooperation between civilian and military actors, including cooperation with North Atlantic Treaty Organisation (NATO), given that a large-scale cyber incident affecting Union civilian infrastructure on which the military rely may also activate NATO response mechanisms.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/library/cyber-blueprint-draft-council-recommendation]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Iran Deploys AI - Guided Missiles &amp; Drones</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Iran’s Revolutionary Guards Corps (IRGC) recently tested AI-powered precision-guided missiles during military exercises in the Persian Gulf, marking a significant advancement in the country’s missile capabilities. The January drills in Bushehr and Khuzestan provinces focused on protecting critical infrastructure, including Iran’s nuclear and petrochemical facilities. Iranian officials claim the AI-driven missiles enhance targeting accuracy and overall performance, with new cruise missiles reportedly exceeding a 1,000 km range. While specific AI technologies remain undisclosed, the development raises concerns amid ongoing tensions between Iran and Israel, potentially impacting regional military dynamics.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cybersecurityintelligence.com/blog/iran-deploys-ai---guided-missiles-8270.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Australia bans Kaspersky</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Secretary of the Department of Home Affairs has today issued a mandatory Direction under the Protective Security Policy Framework (PSPF) to government entities to manage a protective security risk to the Commonwealth. This Direction requires Australian Government entities to prevent the installation of Kaspersky Lab, Inc. products and web services from all Australian Government systems and devices, and where found, to remove all existing instances.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://cyberinsider.com/australia-bans-kaspersky-software-over-national-security-concerns/">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.protectivesecurity.gov.au/news/pspf-direction-update-kaspersky-lab-inc-products-and-web-services]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>North Korean APT-C-28 Expands Cyber Espionage Campaign</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A recent report from 360 Threat Intelligence Center highlights the ongoing cyber espionage activities of North Korea-linked APT-C-28 (ScarCruft), also known as APT37 or Group123. Active since at least 2012, the group targets South Korea and other Asian nations, focusing on strategic industries such as aerospace, electronics, and healthcare. ScarCruft primarily relies on RokRat, a cloud-based remote access Trojan (RAT), delivered through spearphishing campaigns using malicious LNK shortcut files and fileless malware techniques. The group has evolved its tactics by shifting away from cloud-based command-and-control servers and embedding payloads directly into LNK files to evade detection.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securityonline.info/north-korean-apt-c-28-expands-cyber-espionage-campaign/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Sticky Werewolf targets Russian and Belarusian organizations with LummaStealer</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Researchers from Kaspersky published a campaign attributed to Sticky Werewolf APT group, informing that recent activity indicates a surge in attacks in January 2025, following previous operations observed in June 2024. The main objective of the group remains data theft, primarily through stealers and remote administration tools to establish full control over infected machines. Sticky Werewolf (alias Angry Likho), tracked since at least 2023, has traditionally focused on large organizations, government agencies, and their contractors. Based on fluent Russian-language bait files, researchers infer that the attackers are likely native Russian speakers.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securelist.com/angry-likho-apt-attacks-with-lumma-stealer/115663/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Salt Typhoon campaigns targeting telecommunications analyzed</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Researchers from Cisco Talos have released an analysis on the widespread campaign targeting major U.S. telecommunications providers attributed to Salt Typhoon, believed to be a Chinese state-sponsored cyberespionage actor. Initially reported in late 2024 and later confirmed by the U.S. government, the campaign primarily involves persistent access to core networking infrastructure, extensive credential harvesting, and infrastructure pivoting.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>According to the recent findings, Salt Typhoon has primarily gained access to Cisco networking devices using legitimate stolen credentials, rather than exploiting vulnerabilities. The only confirmed instance of vulnerability exploitation involved CVE-2018-0171, a known Cisco vulnerability. Other reported cases of vulnerability abuse, including CVE-2023-20198, CVE-2023-20273, and CVE-2024-20399, remain unverified.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://blog.talosintelligence.com/salt-typhoon-analysis/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>How malicious AI powers the latest surge of advanced email threats</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Email remains the primary attack vector for cybercriminals, with business email compromise (BEC) and vendor email compromise (VEC) attacks surging by 54% between 2023 and 2024. The rise of malicious AI tools has made phishing attacks more sophisticated, allowing threat actors to generate highly convincing emails that bypass traditional security measures. Attackers exploit personal data, multichannel phishing tactics, and outdated security tools to evade detection. Overreliance on employee awareness training and legacy defenses further weakens protection. To counter these threats, organizations must adopt AI-powered threat detection to proactively identify and mitigate evolving cyber risks.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.scworld.com/perspective/how-malicious-ai-powers-the-latest-surge-of-advanced-email-threats]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 February, 2025></pubDate>	
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Ukrainian hackers claim breach of Russian loan company linked to Putin’s ex-wife</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The pro-Ukraine hacking group Cyber Alliance has claimed responsibility for a cyberattack on CarMoney, a major Russian microfinance firm reportedly linked to President Vladimir Putin’s ex-wife, Lyudmila Ocheretnaya. The attack forced CarMoney to shut down its systems after hackers sent false messages to customers, claiming the company was closing and forgiving debts. While CarMoney insists no personal data was compromised, the hackers claim to have obtained borrower information, including details on Russian military personnel. This incident follows a series of cyberattacks by the Ukrainian Cyber Alliance targeting Russian entities since the 2022 invasion of Ukraine.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://therecord.media/russia-carmoney-data-breach-ukrainian-cyber-alliance]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>UK government proposes ransomware legislation to curb payments and boost reporting</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 19, the UK's home office reported the UK government's consultation on ransomware legislation aimed at reducing payments to cybercriminals and increasing incident reporting. Proposed measures seek to limit financial incentives for attackers, improve intelligence on ransomware transactions, and enhance government response capabilities. The consultation remains open until April 8, 2025, with responses invited from stakeholders.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.gov.uk/government/consultations/ransomware-proposals-to-increase-incident-reporting-and-reduce-payments-to-criminals]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Pegasus spyware infected private sector devices and at least on Europe government official</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 19, iVerify, a US based cybersecurity firm, reported new detections of Pegasus spyware on 11 out of 18,000 devices tested in December, including those of business executives in real estate, logistics, and finance, as well as a European government official. The findings suggest broader use of commercial spyware beyond civil society targets. Some victims were monitored for years using multiple Pegasus variants.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://iverify.io/blog/how-democratizing-threat-hunting-is-changing-mobile-security]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Italy is under DDoS siege</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>For the third consecutive day, the pro-Russian hacker group Noname057(16) has carried out a wave of cyberattacks targeting Italy. On Wednesday, the group's latest offensive focused on financial institutions, arms manufacturers, and public transportation companies.</p> 
		<p></p>
		<p>Earlier this week, the hackers targeted around 20 websites, including those of Italy’s Guardia di Finanza, the Carabinieri, and multiple government ministries—Industry and Made in Italy, Foreign Affairs, Economy, Infrastructure and Transport, and Economic Development.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/politics/news/pro-russian-hackers-target-italy-for-the-third-consecutive-day-in-retaliation-for-mattarellas-remarks/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>FBI Warns of Ghost Ransomware Attacks Targeting 70 Countries</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), and the Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center (MS-ISAC) are releasing this joint advisory to disseminate known Ghost (Cring)— (“Ghost”)—ransomware IOCs and TTPs identified through FBI investigation as recently as January 2025.</p> 
		<p></p>
		<p>Beginning early 2021, Ghost actors began attacking victims whose internet facing services ran outdated versions of software and firmware. This indiscriminate targeting of networks containing vulnerabilities has led to the compromise of organizations across more than 70 countries, including organizations in China. Ghost actors, located in China, conduct these widespread attacks for financial gain. Affected victims include critical infrastructure, schools and universities, healthcare, government networks, religious institutions, technology and manufacturing companies, and numerous small- and medium-sized businesses.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.ic3.gov/CSA/2025/250219.pdf]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Microsoft’s Majorana 1 chip carves new path for quantum computing</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft introduced Majorana 1, the world’s first quantum chip powered by a new Topological Core architecture that it expects will realize quantum computers capable of solving meaningful, industrial-scale problems in years, not decades.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>It leverages the world’s first topoconductor, a breakthrough type of material which can observe and control Majorana particles to produce more reliable and scalable qubits, which are the building blocks for quantum computers.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The topoconductor, or topological superconductor, is a special category of material that can create an entirely new state of matter – not a solid, liquid or gas but a topological state. This is harnessed to produce a more stable qubit that is fast, small and can be digitally controlled, without the tradeoffs required by current alternatives.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://news.microsoft.com/source/features/innovation/microsofts-majorana-1-chip-carves-new-path-for-quantum-computing/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Analysis of an attack conducted by NSA</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A cybersecurity researcher investigated how Chinese cybersecurity entities attribute cyber operations to the NSA, labeled as “APT-C-40.” Drawing from reports by Qihoo 360, Pangu Lab, and China’s National Computer Virus Emergency Response Center, the study examined claims that NSA’s Tailored Access Operations (TAO) allegedly hacked China’s Northwestern Polytechnical University in 2022 using sophisticated malware and zero-day exploits. The attack reportedly leveraged phishing, network traffic hijacking, and persistent backdoors to steal sensitive data. Chinese investigators attributed the breach to NSA based on working hours, language settings, and tool similarities with previously leaked cyber arsenals. The research also highlighted differences in Western and Chinese incident response methodologies, emphasizing China’s focus on big data analysis and collaboration across cybersecurity entities.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.inversecos.com/2025/02/an-inside-look-at-nsa-equation-group.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>China-linked APT41 targets japanese firms in RevivalStone cyberespionage campaign</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 18, Japanese cybersecurity company LAC reported that China-linked APT41 targeted Japanese manufacturing, materials, and energy sectors in a campaign dubbed RevivalStone. Active since at least 2012, Winnti deployed new malware variants in 2024, exploiting an SQL injection vulnerability in an ERP system to drop web shells. The group used stolen certificates and rootkits for persistence and covert access.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.lac.co.jp/lacwatch/report/20250213_004283.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Mustang Panda novel techniques detected</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Security researchers from TrendMicro have identified a Chinese state-sponsored cyber campaign conducted by Mustang Panda (also tracked as Earth Preta), which is leveraging Microsoft Application Virtualization Injector (MAVInject) to bypass ESET antivirus detection and deploy a TONESHELL backdoor variant. The campaign primarily targets government entities in the Asia-Pacific region, utilizing spearphishing tactics to deliver its payload.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.trendmicro.com/en_no/research/25/b/earth-preta-mixes-legitimate-and-malicious-components-to-sidestep-detection.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>GreenBravo novel infrastructure detected</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Among the newly observed TTPs, Recorded Future identified evidence that GreenBravo operators have registered infrastructure using Onion Mail accounts and pivoted to bulletproof hosting providers such as Stark Industries Solutions.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Historically, Recorded Future observed GreenBravo infrastructure linked to attacks targeting Israeli academics and Iranian investigative journalists. While no active targeting has surfaced at this time, the server configurations, matching Document Object Model (DOM) hashes, domain naming conventions, and use of specific infrastructure providers strongly indicate that the newly identified clusters are linked to this Iran-nexus group.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[Leonardo, URL is not disclosed]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russian Government Proposes Stricter Penalties to Tackle Cybercrime</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 10, 2025, Russia approved sweeping cybersecurity reforms aimed at combating rising cyber threats by imposing harsher penalties, expanding law enforcement powers, and introducing public trials for cybercriminals. The legislation increases prison sentences to up to 15 years for hacking and infrastructure attacks, allows asset seizures—including cryptocurrencies—and bans convicted offenders from IT and finance jobs for a decade. Intelligence agencies gain enhanced surveillance tools, while companies face stricter security mandates. The reforms also streamline international extradition for cyber suspects, though critics warn of diplomatic tensions and privacy risks. If enacted, Russia’s cybercrime laws would be among the world’s strictest, with significant implications for digital governance and global cybersecurity cooperation.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://gbhackers.com/russian-government-proposes-stricter-penalties/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>North Korea's Kimsuky Taps Trusted Platforms to Attack South Korea</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A recent campaign by North Korea-linked Kimsuky, dubbed DEEP#DRIVE by Securonix, highlights the group's increasing use of stealthy living-off-the-land techniques and trusted services like Dropbox to evade detection. The attack involved phishing emails distributing fake documents that executed PowerShell scripts to gather system data and download additional malware. While some activity targeted cryptocurrency users, the primary focus was espionage against South Korean government agencies and businesses. Researchers identified signs of over 8,000 compromised systems, with Kimsuky demonstrating improved operational security by using OAuth-based authentication for Dropbox storage and quickly dismantling infrastructure when detected. Experts recommend organizations implement stricter PowerShell execution policies, restrict shortcut file execution, and strengthen phishing defenses to counter such threats.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.darkreading.com/cyberattacks-data-breaches/north-koreans-kimsuky-attacks-rivals-trusted-platforms]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>19 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russian state hackers spy on Ukrainian military through Signal app</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Russian state-backed hackers are increasingly targeting Signal messenger accounts, particularly those used by Ukrainian military personnel and government officials, to intercept sensitive communications. Google’s security team reports that hackers exploit Signal’s “linked devices” feature by distributing malicious QR codes disguised as legitimate invites or security alerts, allowing attackers to access messages in real time. Some operations involve battlefield-captured devices, while others use phishing kits mimicking Ukrainian military applications. Russian groups, including Sandworm and UNC4221, have also deployed malware to exfiltrate Signal messages. While these attacks are driven by wartime intelligence needs, experts warn that similar threats could expand to other regions and secure messaging apps. Signal is working to enhance its security protections against such exploits.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://therecord.media/russian-state-hackers-spy-on-ukraine-military-signal]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>DIU and the Armed Forces of Ukraine punished Gazprom for millions of dollars</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 7-8, Ukrainian cyber specialists from the Defence Intelligence and Armed Forces of Ukraine launched a large-scale cyberattack on Russia's oil and gas infrastructure, primarily targeting Gazstroyprom, a key contractor of Gazprom, along with 22 other affiliated companies. The operation disabled over 120 servers and 10,000 computers, halting critical systems and destroying 2,000 terabytes of documentation. The attack caused significant disruption to companies supporting Russia’s military efforts, with estimated damages reaching tens to hundreds of millions of dollars.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://unn.ua/en/news/the-gur-and-the-armed-forces-of-ukraine-punished-gazprom-for-millions-of-dollars-a-source-disclosed-the-details-of-the-cyberattack]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Telegram Abused as C2 Channel for New Golang Backdoor</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Netskope Threat Labs has identified a new Go-based backdoor malware, likely of Russian origin, that uses Telegram as its command and control (C2) channel. Discovered during threat hunting activities, the malware is fully functional despite appearing to be under development. It supports commands to execute PowerShell scripts, relaunch itself for persistence, and self-destruct, with all outputs sent to the Telegram channel. The use of Telegram for C2 makes detection difficult, as it blends with normal cloud app traffic. Netskope Advanced Threat Protection detects this threat as Trojan.Generic.37477095.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.netskope.com/blog/telegram-abused-as-c2-channel-for-new-golang-backdoor]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Password managers under increasing threat as infostealers triple and adapt</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Picus Security reports a three-fold increase in malware targeting credentials stored in password managers and browser-based login vaults, marking a significant shift in cybercriminal tactics. Based on an analysis of one million malware samples, the study found that 93% of attacks align with just 10 MITRE ATT&amp;CK techniques. Infostealers such as RedLine and Lumma, the latter offered as malware-as-a-service, are driving this surge by harvesting credentials from browsers, dedicated password managers, and cloud secrets management tools. Picus Labs co-founder Dr. Suleyman Ozarslan attributes the trend to stronger defenses in modern operating systems, which have pushed attackers to target less-protected credential stores.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.csoonline.com/article/3825453/password-managers-under-increasing-threat-as-infostealers-triple-and-adapt.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>18 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Black-Hat SEO Poisioning Attacks Exploit Indian Government and Financial Websites</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A large-scale black-hat SEO poisoning campaign has compromised over 150 Indian government and financial institution websites, redirecting millions of users to fraudulent gambling platforms promoting rummy and high-risk “investment” games. Exploiting vulnerabilities in .gov.in and .ac.in domains, attackers injected malicious JavaScript to hijack search engine rankings, directing mobile users to gambling sites while showing error pages to desktop visitors to evade detection. Analysts discovered over 12,000 spam pages on government servers using .shtml and .aspx uploads with financial keywords to dominate search results. The attackers leveraged Cloudflare and AWS infrastructure to mask their operations, deploying phishing kits mimicking banking portals. Victims lured with fake bonuses reported losses of ₹50,000–₹2 lakh, while takedowns by CERT-In and Google have been slowed by the campaign’s scale. With losses exceeding ₹200 crore annually, cybersecurity experts urge enhanced website audits, search ranking monitoring, and stricter file-upload controls to counter future threats.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://gbhackers.com/black-hat-seo-poisioning-attack/#google_vignette]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>An Italian journalist speaks about being targeted with Paragon spyware</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Francesco Cancellato, editor-in-chief of the Italian newspaper Fanpage, revealed he was targeted by spyware from Paragon Solutions via WhatsApp, alongside three other journalists critical of the Italian government. Cancellato, known for undercover investigations into far-right political parties, including Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni's Brothers of Italy, suspects the attack originated in Italy but cannot confirm government involvement. He chose to go public to highlight the growing misuse of spyware against journalists and activists, warning of its impact on press freedom and democracy.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://therecord.media/italian-journalist-speaks-about-being-targeted-spyware]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cyberattack on the University of the Bundeswehr Munich</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Bundeswehr University in Munich experienced a cyberattack on its data centre, detected on 23 January 2025, with attackers accessing a central IT service. The university, which trains Bundeswehr personnel in fields such as cybersecurity and intelligence, is working to assess and mitigate the impact, though only internal university systems were affected. While there is no evidence of data deletion or encryption, reports suggest that personal information of students and staff, including bank details and phone numbers, may be compromised.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.heise.de/news/Cyberattacke-auf-die-Universitaet-der-Bundeswehr-Muenchen-10281927.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>17 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Propaganda Watch: China’s International Communication Centres</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>China’s International Communication Centres (ICCs), operated under the Central Propaganda Department of the Chinese Communist Party (CCP), aim to shape global narratives and promote pro-Beijing messaging. Since their launch in 2018, over 100 centres have been established, with operations expanding globally through media partnerships and social media campaigns. ICCs use tactics such as AI-generated content, collaboration with foreign influencers, and covert social media accounts to influence public opinion, while also targeting sensitive issues like Taiwan and Tibet through regional messaging initiatives.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://greydynamics.com/propaganda-watch-chinas-international-communication-centres/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Alleged data leak at Leonardo</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The ransomware leak page associated with the victim identified as Leonardo, a well-known global aerospace, defense, and security company, details a significant data breach affecting their operations. According to the extracted information, the ransomware group’s name is threeam, and they have disclosed data regarding 39 users and 62 third-party entities. Shortly after the claim Leonardo has issued a public statement, reading "Leonardo states that rumors claiming the hacker group ThreeAM breached Leonardo Spa's computer systems are completely unfounded."</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://x.com/Leonardo_IT/status/1890142102434250997">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.redpacketsecurity.com/threeam-ransomware-victim-leonardo-com/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russian influence operations evolving ahead German Federal elections</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>State-affiliated influence operations aiming at interfering with German federal elections scheduled for February 23, 2025. Key objectives of these influence operations include fomenting domestic unrest, manipulating public discourse, eroding trust in election security, and promoting skepticism toward the EU and NATO. Moreover, these campaigns seek to amplify criticism of the United States while fostering support for political entities such as Alternative für Deutschland (AfD), perceived as aligning with Russian strategic interests.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/stimmen-aus-moskau-russian-influence-operations-target-german-elections]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Japan approves Cyber Defense Bill to counter sophisticated threats</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 7, Japan's Cabinet approved the Cyber Response Capability Enhancement Bill to strengthen defenses against sophisticated cyberattacks targeting critical infrastructure. This legislation aligns with the National Security Strategy (December 2022) and incorporates expert recommendations from November 29, 2024. The bill includes active cyber defense measures, such as proactively detecting threats and shutting down enemy servers during an incident to mitigate potential harm.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cas.go.jp/jp/seisaku/cyber_anzen_hosyo_torikumi/index.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>North Korea targets crypto developers via NPM supply chain attack</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>North Korea's Lazarus Group has launched a new cyber campaign, Operation Marstech Mayhem, targeting Web3 developers and cryptocurrency wallets by embedding the Marstech1 implant into NPM packages and GitHub repositories. According to SecurityScorecard, attackers use stolen API keys and obfuscated JavaScript code to compromise wallets across Windows, macOS, and Linux, affecting at least 233 victims so far. The implant enables Lazarus to access and steal cryptocurrency funds, exploiting the software supply chain to spread the malware more widely. Meanwhile, Microsoft reported that Kimsuky, another North Korean group, has been impersonating South Korean officials to trick victims into running malicious PowerShell commands for espionage purposes. The incidents highlight North Korea's continued focus on financially and strategically motivated cyber operations.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theregister.com/2025/02/13/north_korea_npm_crypto/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>14 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Ukraine warns of growing AI use in Russian cyber-espionage operations</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Russian state-backed hackers are increasingly using AI to analyse stolen data, making their cyber operations more precise and effective, according to Ukrainian cyber officials. By applying machine learning, attackers filter essential information from compromised mailboxes to create highly personalised phishing messages targeting military personnel. These messages often include names, ranks, and official documents to deceive victims into clicking malicious links. Ukraine has also observed growing collaboration between Russian hackers and cybercriminal groups, with AI used to process stolen data for espionage. The use of AI in Russian cyber campaigns has raised concerns globally, with officials warning about potential applications like deepfake propaganda and enhanced infrastructure attacks.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://therecord.media/russia-ukraine-cyber-espionage-artificial-intelligence]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Microsoft uncovers BadPilot campaign by Russian Seashell Blizzard subgroup</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 12, Microsoft revealed that a subgroup within the Russian state actor Seashell Blizzard (aka Sandworm) has been conducting a multiyear global access operation, termed the "BadPilot campaign." This subgroup exploited vulnerabilities in internet-facing infrastructure to persist on high-value targets across sectors like energy, telecommunications, and government, expanding their operations beyond Eastern Europe since at least 2021.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/security/blog/2025/02/12/the-badpilot-campaign-seashell-blizzard-subgroup-conducts-multiyear-global-access-operation/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Salt Typhoon Exploits Vulnerable Cisco Devices of Global Telecommunications Providers</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Between December 2024 and January 2025, the Chinese state-sponsored group RedMike, linked to Salt Typhoon, exploited unpatched Cisco network devices targeting global telecommunications providers, including affiliates in the US, UK, South Africa, and several universities across multiple countries. The group gained access through vulnerabilities to establish persistent access and monitor communications, likely for intelligence gathering. RedMike targeted over 1,000 devices, with a focus on critical infrastructure and academic institutions conducting research in telecommunications and technology.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/redmike-salt-typhoon-exploits-vulnerable-devices]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Kimsuky uses PowerShell exploits to target international affairs professionals and NGOs</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 11, Microsoft reported that North Korea-linked Kimsuky, also known as Emerald Sleet, is using a tactic where victims are deceived into running PowerShell as an administrator and executing malicious code. This facilitates data exfiltration via a remote desktop tool. The group primarily targets individuals working in international affairs, particularly those focused on Northeast Asia, in America, Europe, and East Asia.	</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://x.com/MsftSecIntel/status/1889407814604296490]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>A new wave of Mirai-based botnet exploiting vulnerabilities in routers and smart devices</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A Mirai-based botnet has been actively exploiting vulnerabilities in routers and smart devices, primarily targeting industrial and home networks globally. The Shadowserver Foundation reported the botnet’s use of flaws in devices from various devices to gain unauthorised access and conduct large-scale Distributed Denial-of-Service (DDoS) attacks. The attackers infiltrate devices by exploiting unpatched vulnerabilities and using brute-force techniques on weak passwords. With around 15,000 active nodes, the botnet appears motivated by financial gain through DDoS-for-hire services.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cybersecuritynews.com/mirai-botnet-exploiting-router-vulnerabilities/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Have I Been Pwned likely to ban resellers from buying subs, citing ‘sh*tty behavior’ and onerous support requests</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Troy Hunt, founder of Have I Been Pwned (HIBP), is considering banning resellers from the service due to their disproportionate demand for support. Although resellers represent only 0.86% of subscribers, they account for over 15% of support requests, often requiring more time and effort to resolve. Hunt noted instances of resellers significantly marking up subscription costs and raising complex queries about pricing and policies. While he is exploring automation to reduce this burden, he remains strongly inclined to discontinue reseller partnerships in the coming weeks. HIBP will continue working with managed service providers (MSPs), who are seen as adding genuine value.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theregister.com/2025/02/13/hibp_reseller_ban/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>LLMjacking exploits target AI models like DeepSeek</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cybercriminals are increasingly targeting emerging AI models like DeepSeek through a tactic known as LLMjacking, which involves stealing API keys and cloud credentials to access these models illicitly. The Sysdig Threat Research Team reported that attackers use covert reverse proxies and dynamic domain names to disguise their activity, allowing them to profit by selling unauthorised access online. Victims face significant financial losses, with one case involving nearly $39,000 in unauthorised charges. The attacks are facilitated through underground forums and tools that help conceal infrastructure.</p>]]> 	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securitybrief.com.au/story/llmjacking-exploits-target-ai-models-like-deepseek-experts-warn]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>13 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cybercrime: A Multifaceted National Security Threat</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mandiant Consulting reported a significant rise in financially motivated cybercrime in 2024, with nearly four times more incidents than state-backed intrusions. Cybercriminals increasingly target critical sectors like healthcare, causing disruptions with impacts similar to state-sponsored attacks. Additionally, cybercrime and state-backed hacking often intersect, with countries like Russia, Iran, China, and North Korea leveraging criminal groups for espionage, disruption, and revenue generation.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/threat-intelligence/cybercrime-multifaceted-national-security-threat]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Internet and social media restriction in Democratic Republic of Congo</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On February 10, third-party monitor Internet Society reported ongoing social media restrictions in the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC). On January 27, internet monitor NetBlocks reported significant internet disruption in Goma. On February 3, NetBlocks further reported multiple mobile application stores were blocked to prevent users from downloading VPNs to circumvent social media restrictions. DRC authorities have suspended internet access since January 23 in an attempt to contain misinformation.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://netblocks.org/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hacker attack on LUP clinics: Medical care remains secure</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The German LUP-Klinikum Helene von Bülow experienced a cyberattack on its electronic systems during the night of February 10. The police were notified on Monday morning, and investigations have been initiated by the Schwerin Criminal Police and the State Criminal Office. As a precaution, the clinics in Hagenow and Ludwigslust were disconnected from email and online services, and their emergency rooms were temporarily deregistered, although critical cases are still being treated. Despite the attack, medical care at all affected locations remains fully operational.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[n/a]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Sandworm APT Targets Ukrainian Users with Trojanized Microsoft KMS Activation Tools in Cyber Espionage Campaigns</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>EclecticIQ analysts report that Sandworm (APT44), a Russian GRU-backed threat actor, is conducting a cyber espionage campaign targeting Ukrainian Windows users. Since late 2023, Sandworm has exploited pirated Microsoft Key Management Service activators and fake Windows updates to deploy BACKORDER, a malware loader that installs Dark Crystal RAT (DcRAT) for data theft and espionage. Evidence linking Sandworm to this campaign includes shared infrastructure, consistent tactics, and the use of Russian-language development tools. Ukraine's widespread reliance on pirated software, especially in government sectors, has significantly increased vulnerability to such attacks, posing risks to national security and critical infrastructure.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://blog.eclecticiq.com/sandworm-apt-targets-ukrainian-users-with-trojanized-microsoft-kms-activation-tools-in-cyber-espionage-campaigns]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>India's Cybercrime Problems Grow as Nation Digitizes</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>India is experiencing a sharp rise in cybercrime, with cyber fraud against citizens increasing by 51% in the past year and businesses facing significantly more cyberattacks than the global average. In 2024, over 1.7 million cybercrime complaints were filed, up from 1.1 million in 2023, with nearly half of the attacks originating from cybercriminal hubs in Cambodia, Myanmar, and Laos. Businesses are increasingly targeted, facing more denial-of-service attacks and threats to mobile APIs. The government is responding with new data protection laws, secure banking domains, international cooperation with the US, and initiatives to train 5,000 cybersecurity professionals, though challenges remain in addressing the growing threat.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.darkreading.com/cyber-risk/indias-cybercrime-problems-nation-digitizes]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Delivering Malware Through Abandoned Amazon S3 Buckets</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Researchers identified and registered around 150 abandoned Amazon S3 buckets, previously used in commercial and open-source software, government systems, and infrastructure pipelines, for just $400. These buckets, though abandoned, still received eight million requests over two months from systems seeking updates, highlighting a major supply-chain vulnerability. Had this been a malicious operation, attackers could have inserted malware into the buckets, leading to widespread compromise similar to the SolarWinds attack but on a larger scale. Since the original developers no longer control these buckets, they can't patch vulnerabilities or notify affected users, exposing significant flaws in software supply-chain security.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2025/02/delivering-malware-through-abandoned-amazon-s3-buckets.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>New Chinese Hacking Campaign Targets Manufacturing Firms to Steal IP</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Check Point is investigating a new Chinese cyber-espionage campaign targeting suppliers in sensitive manufacturing sectors, including chemical products and infrastructure components, in the US and globally. According to Lotem Finkelsteen, Check Point's Director of Threat Intelligence, the hackers are infiltrating networks via vulnerabilities in edge devices like IoT equipment and virtual private servers, aiming to steal intellectual property and gain insights into supply chains. While the group shares tactics with known Chinese state-sponsored actors, specific attribution is pending. The full report will be released soon, highlighting the growing aggressiveness of Chinese cyber activities despite increased exposure.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/news/new-chinese-hacking-ip-theft/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>12 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>U.S. adversaries increasingly turning to cybercriminals and their malware for help</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A Google report reveals that countries like Russia, China, Iran, and North Korea are increasingly leveraging cybercriminal tools and networks to advance their cyber-espionage efforts. Russia, driven by the war in Ukraine, has been using malware commonly associated with cybercriminals, such as Radthief and Warzone, to support its operations. This trend is attributed to resource constraints and operational demands, making criminal tools a cheaper and more deniable option. Other nations, like China, have also used cybercriminal groups to mask their espionage activities. Google warns that this growing overlap between state and criminal cyber actors poses a significant national security threat.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cyberscoop.com/u-s-adversaries-increasingly-turning-to-cybercriminals-and-their-malware-for-help/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Global police operation seizes 8base ransomware gang leak site</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>An international coalition of law enforcement agencies from Europe, Japan, the U.S., and the U.K. has seized the dark web leak site of the 8base ransomware gang, a financially motivated hacking group first identified in 2022. The Bavarian State Criminal Police Office led the operation on behalf of the Public Prosecutor General in Bamberg, with the U.K.’s National Crime Agency confirming its supportive role. 8base, linked to the RansomHouse extortion group, is known for double-extortion tactics—encrypting victims' data and threatening to leak it unless ransoms are paid. The group has targeted multiple sectors in the U.S., including healthcare, and previously claimed responsibility for a cyberattack on the United Nations Development Programme.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://techcrunch.com/2025/02/10/global-police-operation-seizes-8base-ransomware-gang-leak-site/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Dutch Minister announces plans for new National Cyber Security Center</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Dutch National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC), the Digital Trust Center (DTC), and the Computer Security Incident Response Team for digital service providers (CSIRT-DSP) will merge into a new, unified NCSC, as announced by Minister Beljaarts. This consolidation aims to improve synergy and reduce fragmentation in the government's cybersecurity landscape. The new NCSC will serve multiple roles, including as a national CSIRT, knowledge and advisory center, execution coordinator, and sector-specific CSIRT, targeting vital sectors like banking, energy, telecom, and the wider business community. This year will focus on joint communication efforts, shared products, and the establishment of an advisory board with external stakeholders to guide strategic decisions. The integration process began last year, with CSIRT-DSP now fully operating under the NCSC, and the complete transition is expected by January next year.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.security.nl/posting/875818/Minister+kondigt+plannen+aan+voor+nieuw+Nationaal+Cyber+Security+Centrum]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Von der Leyen launches world’s largest public-private partnership to win AI race</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Ursula von der Leyen announced a €50 billion investAI initiative and an additional €8 billion for AI Factories during the AI Action Summit in Paris, signaling the EU's strong commitment to advancing in the global AI race. Emphasizing growth and investment, von der Leyen highlighted that these funds will complement the €150 billion private EU AI Champions initiative, creating the largest public-private AI partnership globally. She also introduced plans for AI Gigafactories, aiming to replicate the collaborative success of CERN and significantly boost private sector involvement, asserting that global leadership in AI is still within reach.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/tech/news/von-der-leyen-launches-worlds-largest-public-private-partnership-to-win-ai-race/)]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>11 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Fast-track armed forces recruitment launched to boost UK cyber defence</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The UK Ministry of Defence has launched a new fast-track recruitment scheme to address the growing cyber threat by accelerating the training and deployment of cyber specialists within the armed forces. Recruits with digital skills will undergo a condensed basic training followed by specialized instruction at the Defence Cyber Academy, enabling them to enter operational roles by the end of 2025. This initiative aims to bolster the UK’s cyber defenses in response to increasing cyberattacks on military networks and is part of the government’s broader effort to tackle recruitment challenges and adapt to the evolving nature of warfare in the digital age.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.gov.uk/government/news/fast-track-armed-forces-recruitment-launched-to-boost-uk-cyber-defence]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Musk’s DOGE poses cybersecurity risks to US federal systems</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>According to a report by The Atlantic on February 7, Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) has accessed critical US federal IT systems, including those of the Treasury Department and Office of Personnel Management. Cybersecurity experts warn that DOGE’s untrained personnel could unintentionally or deliberately compromise these systems, posing national security risks. The full impact is unclear, but concerns grow over data breaches, system disruptions, and long-term cybersecurity threats.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2025/02/elon-musk-doge-security/681600/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Commission to withdraw proposed ePrivacy Regulation</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>----I only have the title, the content is behind paywall and I was not able to find alternative source at the time of reporting----</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/tech/news/commission-to-withdraw-proposed-eprivacy-regulation]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hackers breach Microsoft IIS services using Cityworks RCE bug</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Hackers are exploiting a high-severity remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability (CVE-2025-0994) in Cityworks, a GIS-based asset and work order management software, to run malicious code on customers' Microsoft IIS web servers. The flaw, identified as a severe deserialization issue, affects critical infrastructure across various U.S. cities and utilities, including Greeley, Baltimore County, and Sacramento Suburban Water District, posing risks of service disruptions, data breaches, and public safety threats. Trimble, the developer of Cityworks, is working on a fix to be included in the next software update and has urged on-premises customers to apply patches immediately, while Cityworks Online deployments will be updated automatically. Investigations revealed overprivileged permissions and misconfigured directories in several deployments, prompting CISA to advise organizations to conduct risk assessments before implementing defensive measures.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.csoonline.com/article/3820852/hackers-breach-microsoft-iis-services-using-cityworks-rce-bug.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Europol Warns Financial Sector of “Imminent” Quantum Threat</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Europol has warned Europe’s financial services sector to start preparing for the transition to quantum-safe cryptography due to the growing threat of "store now, decrypt later" (SNDL) attacks. These attacks involve cybercriminals stealing encrypted data today with the intention of decrypting it in the future, once quantum computers—capable of breaking current public key cryptography—become available. While such quantum machines are expected to be at least a decade away, accelerated scientific breakthroughs and increased funding could shorten this timeline. Failure to act could jeopardize the security of financial transactions, authentication processes, and digital contracts, posing significant risks to the financial sector.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/news/europol-warns-financial-sector/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>10 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>OpenAI investigates potential leak of 20 million users' data</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cybercriminals claim to have stolen login data from over 20 million OpenAI accounts, raising serious concerns about potential data breaches affecting ChatGPT users. The data, advertised on a darknet forum, includes email addresses and passwords being sold cheaply, though researchers and security experts remain skeptical about the legitimacy of these claims. OpenAI has stated that there is no evidence of a system compromise but is actively investigating the situation and may conduct a mass review of accounts. If confirmed, the breach could expose sensitive user data, including confidential company projects and communications, significantly impacting user trust and security.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.heise.de/en/news/Cyberattack-OpenAI-investigates-potential-leak-of-20-million-users-data-10275551.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>North Korean APT Kimsuky Uses forceCopy Malware to Steal Browser-Stored Credentials</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The North Korean hacking group Kimsuky, also known as APT43, has been carrying out targeted phishing attacks to steal sensitive information, according to AhnLab Security Intelligence Center (ASEC). These attacks use deceptive emails to trick victims into opening malicious attachments, allowing the hackers to gain access to their systems. Once inside, Kimsuky deploys various tools to steal login credentials, monitor user activity, and maintain long-term access to the compromised networks. This marks a shift in the group’s tactics, as they increasingly rely on new methods to strengthen their control over targeted systems. The attacks pose serious risks, particularly to organizations handling sensitive data, as Kimsuky is linked to North Korea’s primary intelligence agency.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thehackernews.com/2025/02/north-korean-apt-kimsuky-uses-lnk-files.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>35% Year-over-Year Decrease in Ransomware Payments, Less than Half of Recorded Incidents Resulted in Victim Payments</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2024, the ransomware landscape underwent significant changes, marked by a 35% decline in ransom payments compared to the previous year. This drop was driven by increased law enforcement actions, stronger international cooperation, and a growing number of victims refusing to pay. In response, attackers adapted by rebranding existing ransomware strains and accelerating their operations, with some groups targeting organizations like Snowflake. Disruptions to major groups like LockBit and BlackCat, alongside high-profile arrests, fragmented the ransomware ecosystem, leading to smaller, less coordinated attacks. Despite an increase in ransomware incidents, fewer victims chose to pay, reflecting improved cyber defenses and resilience. However, the evolving tactics of attackers and the rise of new ransomware strains highlight the ongoing threat and need for continued vigilance.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com/blog/crypto-crime-ransomware-victim-extortion-2025/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russian role in buying software for EU border system probed</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>European prosecutors are investigating how the Moscow office of French IT firm Atos contributed to building the EU’s new electronic border system, which will create the bloc’s largest personal information database. Atos used its Russian staff to procure software for the project in 2021, raising significant security concerns due to the potential access of Russia’s FSB security service, as Atos Russia operated under an FSB license. Although no security breaches have been identified, and Atos has since divested from its Russian operations, the involvement of Moscow-based staff in such a sensitive project has prompted scrutiny from the European Public Prosecutor’s Office and the EU’s anti-fraud watchdog, Olaf. This situation has delayed the project’s launch and highlighted vulnerabilities in the EU’s handling of critical infrastructure security.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.ft.com/content/15412552-32e3-4ec5-afc3-074cfeac20cb]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>UK government demands Apple backdoor to encrypted cloud data: report</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>UK government officials have reportedly ordered Apple to create a backdoor granting authorities access to all users' encrypted iCloud data under the Investigatory Powers Act 2016, known as the Snoopers' Charter. The demand, issued in January, seeks broad, unrestricted access to encrypted files globally, rather than targeting specific accounts. In response, Apple is expected to withdraw its Advanced Data Protection service from UK users, limiting the impact to the UK while maintaining encryption protections elsewhere, including in the US. This move raises significant privacy concerns, as Apple has previously warned that such backdoors could also be exploited by hackers, compromising user security worldwide.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://techcrunch.com/2025/02/07/uk-government-demands-apple-backdoor-to-encrypted-cloud-data-report/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>7 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>India's RBI Introduces Exclusive &quot;bank.in&quot; Domain to Combat Digital Banking Fraud</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced the introduction of a dedicated "bank.in" internet domain exclusively for Indian banks to combat rising digital financial fraud. This initiative aims to reduce cybersecurity threats like phishing and strengthen trust in digital banking by ensuring more secure financial services. The Institute for Development and Research in Banking Technology (IDRBT) will oversee domain registrations, set to begin in April 2025. Additionally, the RBI plans to launch a separate "fin.in" domain for non-bank financial entities and implement Additional Factor of Authentication (AFA) for cross-border online transactions, adding another layer of security to digital payments. These measures are designed to enhance user confidence and safeguard the integrity of India's digital financial ecosystem.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thehackernews.com/2025/02/indias-rbi-introduces-exclusive-bankin.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Baltics brace for cyberattacks as they depart Russian electricity grid</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Europe’s Baltics are bracing for cyberattacks as they plan to decouple from a Soviet-era joint power grid with Russia and Belarus this weekend.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Estonia has prepared for many possible risk scenarios regarding our departure from BRELL, including cyberthreats,” Gert Auväärt, head of Estonia’s Cyber Security Centre, told POLITICO in a written response. He said the country is ready to call in its cyber reserve, which includes the Estonian Defense League’s cyber unit, a volunteer group of cyber defenders.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.politico.eu/article/baltics-brace-cyberattacks-depart-russian-electricity-grid-brell/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>France releases report about manipulation of information targeting 2024 Romanian presidential elections</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The French General Secretariat for Defense and National Security has issued a report that provides information on the manipulations of the information that targeted the Romanian presidential election of 2024, the results of which were cancelled by the Romanian Constitutional Court on 6 December. Most of the evidence presented came from an analysis carried out between 25 November and 20 December 2024, which relates in particular to the operating procedures observed on the TikTok platform, intended to artificially promote certain contents, as well as the instrumentalization of influences.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.sgdsn.gouv.fr/publications/manipulation-dalgorithmes-et-instrumentalisation-dinfluenceurs-enseignements-de]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>UK technology heads priorities cybersecurity in 2025</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A recent BIE report reveals that UK technology leaders are prioritizing cybersecurity in 2025 due to rising cyber threats linked to AI and digital transformation. Surveying 255 senior leaders, the report highlights that 50% of businesses faced security breaches in the past year, costing the economy billions. Despite improved data governance from Chief Data Officers, challenges in sourcing cybersecurity expertise persist, compounded by a significant technology skills gap acknowledged by 98% of respondents. With AI enabling more sophisticated cyber-attacks, leaders are increasingly reliant on interim cybersecurity professionals to bridge skill gaps, mitigate risks during business transformations, and fast-track growth while addressing issues like legacy systems, budget constraints, and resistance to change.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securitybrief.co.uk/story/uk-technology-heads-prioritise-cybersecurity-in-2025)]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>6 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>21% of CISOs pressured to not report compliance issues</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A study of 600 CISOs worldwide reveals that 21% of security leaders have faced pressure from executives or board members to avoid reporting compliance issues, highlighting a growing conflict between corporate interests and regulatory obligations. While 59% of CISOs indicated they would become whistleblowers if compliance was ignored, many are caught between personal liability risks and organizational pressure to protect reputations. Increased regulatory scrutiny under frameworks like GDPR, SEC rules, and DORA has intensified these challenges, with CISOs often lacking sufficient budgetary and executive support to ensure compliance. This tension is contributing to job dissatisfaction, with nearly 25% of security leaders considering leaving their roles, emphasizing the need for stronger security governance, board-level commitment, and a culture of compliance.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.csoonline.com/article/3818068/21-of-cisos-pressured-to-not-report-compliance-issues.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russian actors exploiting 7-Zip vulnerability to deliver SmokeLoader against Ukrainian targets</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In September 2024, researchers from Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) Threat Hunting Team identified the exploitation of a now-patched zero-day vulnerability in 7-Zip, indexed with CVE-2025-0411, as part of a Russian cyberespionage campaign targeting Ukrainian entities. The vulnerability, patched in 7-Zip version 24.09 released on November 30, 2024, if exploited, allows attackers to bypass Windows Mark-of-the-Web (MoTW) protections, enabling the execution of malicious files without standard security warnings. The campaign leveraged homoglyph attacks to disguise malicious payloads as legitimate documents, increasing the likelihood of successful exploitation. In such attacks, attackers deceive victims by manipulating file names using Cyrillic homoglyph characters, making malicious executables appear as legitimate Microsoft Word documents.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.trendmicro.com/en_us/research/25/a/cve-2025-0411-ukrainian-organizations-targeted.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hackers Using Fake Microsoft ADFS Login Pages to Steal Credentials</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A global phishing campaign is underway, exploiting a legacy Microsoft authentication system to steal user credentials and bypass multi-factor authentication (MFA), targeting over 150 organizations. The attackers employ a combination of social engineering and technical manipulation. Phishing emails, mimicking legitimate notifications, lure victims to spoofed ADFS login pages. These emails often use urgent tones, warn of supposed updates or policy changes, and incorporate legitimate branding, logos, and even contact information to appear genuine.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://hackread.com/hackers-fake-microsoft-adfs-login-pages-steal-credentials/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Massive Malware Repository Discovered on GitHub</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A GitHub repository named “The-MALWARE-Repo,” has come under scrutiny for hosting hundreds of malware samples, including Remote Access Trojans (RATs), ransomware, spyware, viruses, worms, and more. Each folder in the repository includes executable files and scripts associated with these malware categories. According to the post from cyberundergroundfeed, While the repository could serve as a valuable resource for malware analysts and cybersecurity researchers, it poses significant risks if accessed irresponsibly.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cyberpress.org/massive-malware-repository-discovered-on-github/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>5 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>After Texas and Italy, Taiwan and Australia also bans Chinese AI DeepSeek</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Taiwan on 04. February banned government departments from using Chinese startup DeepSeek's artificial intelligence (AI) service as it was a security risk, toughening language from last week which said it should not be used.
		During a cabinet meeting, Taiwan Premier Cho Jung-tai said DeepSeek was banned from use in all government agencies "to ensure the country's information security", his office said in a statement.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>There were also concerns about censorship on DeepSeek and the risk of data ending up in China, the statement said.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Australia has banned DeepSeek from all government devices on the advice of security agencies, a top official said on Wednesday (05. February), citing privacy and malware risks posed by China's breakout AI programme.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Risks included that uploaded information "might not be kept private", government cyber security envoy Andrew Charlton told national broadcaster ABC, and that applications such as DeepSeek "may expose you to malware".</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwan-bans-government-departments-using-deepseek-ai-2025-02-03/">Reference</a></p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/technology/tech-news/after-us-italy-and-taiwan-another-country-ban-deepseek-on-government-devices/articleshow/117922102.cms">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.channelnewsasia.com/world/australia-bans-deepseek-government-devices-privacy-malware-4917296]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Kazakhstan launches internal investigations over UAC-0063 attacks</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Kazakhstan has announced plans to audit its Foreign Ministry following an intrusion that cybersecurity researchers suspect may have ties to Russian state-sponsored operations. The Kazakh Digital Ministry launched an investigation after a recent analysis detailed a cyberespionage campaign targeting diplomatic entities across Central Asia, including Kazakhstan.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://orda.kz/srochnuju-proverku-provedut-v-mid-rk-posle-ataki-rossijskih-hakerov-397634/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Swedish authorities release seized cargo ship ruling out sabotage in Baltic Sea cable incidents</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Swedish Prosecution Authority (SPA) announced that it is releasing the Vezhen, a cargo ship previously suspected of sabotaging a communications cable in the Baltic Sea. Investigators determined that the cable break was not an act of sabotage, but instead resulted from a combination of weather conditions, equipment deficiencies, and seamanship errors.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The Vezhen was seized on January 26. Swedish authorities have now concluded their investigations finding that although the ship was confirmed to be responsible for the cable break, no indications of deliberate interference were found.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://via.tt.se/pressmeddelande/3776460/prosecutor-revokes-decision-on-seized-ship]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Contec Patient Monitors Not Malicious, but Still Pose Big Risk to Healthcare</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Contec CMS8000 patient monitors, widely used in healthcare, have been found to contain an insecure design flaw that exposes patient data and enables potential remote attacks, according to cybersecurity firm Claroty. While the US cybersecurity agency CISA and the FDA initially classified the issue as a hidden backdoor, Claroty clarifies that the hardcoded IP address involved is explicitly documented in the product manual for Central Management System (CMS) connections. The flaw allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via insecure firmware updates, though physical access is required to trigger this process. Additionally, the device communicates with a publicly routable IP, posing risks of data leakage and malicious commands. Claroty demonstrated a proof-of-concept attack confirming remote exploitation potential and recommends blocking the 202.114.4.0/24 subnet, restricting network access, and replacing vulnerable devices unless the firmware is updated.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.securityweek.com/contec-patient-monitors-not-malicious-but-still-pose-big-risk-to-healthcare/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>4 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Chinese-Linked APT Targets Telecoms in South Asia</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Unit 42 researchers uncovered a cyberespionage campaign, CL-STA-0048, targeting high-value organizations in South Asia, including a telecom company, with evidence suggesting a Chinese state-backed APT group. The attackers persistently exploited vulnerable internet-facing services, eventually breaching an unpatched MSSQL server to escalate privileges and deploy malware. They employed stealthy exfiltration techniques, including DNS-based data theft via ping commands and SQLcmd for extracting sensitive information. PlugX RAT played a central role, utilizing DLL sideloading to evade detection, while Cobalt Strike and privilege escalation tools enabled persistence. The attackers leveraged SoftEther VPN and a custom downloader for C2 communications and used a unique "Hex Staging" method for malware deployment. Unit 42 linked CL-STA-0048 to Chinese APT groups like DragonRank, based on shared TTPs, infrastructure, and malware use.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://securityonline.info/cl-sta-0048-chinese-linked-apt-targets-telecoms-in-south-asia/">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/espionage-campaign-targets-south-asian-entities/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>3 February, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Law enforcement takes down two largest cybercrime forums in the world</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A Europol-supported operation, led by German authorities and involving law enforcement from eight countries, has led to the takedown of the two largest cybercrime forums in the world. The two platforms, Cracked and Nulled, had more than 10 million users in total. Both of these underground economy forums offered a quick entry point into the cybercrime scene. These sites worked as one-stop shops and were used not only for discussions on cybercrime but also as marketplaces for illegal goods and cybercrime-as-a-service, such as stolen data, malware or hacking tools. Investigators estimate that suspects earned EUR 1 million in criminal profits.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.europol.europa.eu/media-press/newsroom/news/law-enforcement-takes-down-two-largest-cybercrime-forums-in-world]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>3 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>OpenAI unveils a new ChatGPT agent for ‘deep research’</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>OpenAI has introduced "deep research," a new AI-powered feature in ChatGPT designed for in-depth and complex research, particularly for professionals in finance, science, policy, and engineering. Available to ChatGPT Pro users with future expansions to Plus, Team, and Enterprise tiers, deep research allows users to query multiple sources, analyze data, and receive detailed, citation-backed responses within 5 to 30 minutes. It leverages an enhanced version of OpenAI’s o3 reasoning model, optimized for web browsing and data analysis, but still has accuracy limitations and potential issues with misinformation. OpenAI plans to add visual outputs and support for specialized data sources in the future.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://techcrunch.com/2025/02/02/openai-unveils-a-new-chatgpt-agent-for-deep-research/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>3 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>EU Commission to take a ‘holistic’ approach against Temu, Shein</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The European Commission is planning a holistic strategy to address the surge in imports from major e-commerce platforms like Temu and Shein, which doubled in 2024 to 4.6 billion low-value goods, mostly from China. The draft proposal includes tightening EU customs rules, enhancing consumer protection enforcement, and implementing environmental regulations requiring producers to manage recycled waste. National customs authorities will receive more resources, and AI will be used to detect illegal goods. A new EU Customs Authority will centralize data processing. Meanwhile, Temu faces an EU investigation under the Digital Services Act (DSA), while Shein, though under DSA regulations, is not currently under formal scrutiny. The draft report is expected to be published on Wednesday.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/tech/news/eu-commission-to-take-a-holistic-approach-against-temu-shein/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>3 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>DeepSeek is being banned for official use (Italy, USA)</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Texas has banned Chinese AI company DeepSeek and social media apps Xiaohongshu (RedNote) and Lemon8 from all state-issued devices, citing concerns over data-harvesting and national security risks. Governor Greg Abbott emphasized the state’s commitment to protecting infrastructure from foreign threats, following similar actions against TikTok. Meanwhile, Italy’s data protection authority (Garante) has blocked DeepSeek’s chatbot service due to insufficient transparency regarding data collection, storage, and legal compliance. The regulator demanded clarification on data sources, processing purposes, and storage locations, but DeepSeek denied its operations in Italy, leading to an ongoing investigation.</p>  
		<p></p>
		<p>The Garante’s order to block DeepSeek's chatbot in Italy took immediate effect after the company’s responses were deemed totally insufficient. DeepSeek removed its AI assistant from Italian app stores but claimed it was not subject to local regulations, refusing to provide further information. Italian authorities warned that non-cooperation would keep the ban in place, with some users still able to access the chatbot. The case has drawn broader European scrutiny, as data regulators in Ireland and France are also questioning DeepSeek over its privacy policies. Italy’s Garante, known for its strict stance on AI-related privacy issues, had previously blocked ChatGPT over EU privacy rule concerns.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/italys-privacy-watchdog-blocks-chinese-ai-app-deepseek-2025-01-30/">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://securityaffairs.com/173764/laws-and-regulations/texas-bans-deepseek-and-rednote-govt-devices.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>3 February, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Spyware distribution campaign over WhatsApp detected</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Guardian reported that WhatsApp intervened to stop a spyware campaign attributed to the Israeli cybersecurity firm Paragon Solutions. The operation reportedly compromised close to 100 individuals, primarily targeting  journalists and civil society figures. The spyware, identified as "Graphite", was suspected of being delivered through malicious PDFs distributed in WhatsApp group chats. Cybersecurity experts pointed out that the attack used a zero-click technique, enabling it to infect devices without user engagement. Following the discovery, WhatsApp demanded that Paragon Solutions halt its activities and signaled that legal action was being considered.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2025/jan/31/whatsapp-israel-spyware]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>31 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Taiwan-Matsu undersea cables cut, suspected Chinese involvement raises concerns</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On January 22, two undersea cables connecting Taiwan and the Matsu Islands were reported broken, with initial faults occurring on January 15. Chunghwa Telecom, Taiwan's largest integrated telecommunications operator, announced that communication between Taiwan and the Matsu Islands was restored on January 24. Authorities suspect that Chinese vessels may have been involved in damaging these cables, raising concerns about potential "gray zone operations" by China to disrupt Taiwan's communications.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.ntd.com/taiwan-undersea-internet-cable-cut-by-chinese-ship_1040437.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>31 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Malware Discovered in Healthcare Patient Monitors</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Traced to Chinese IP Address The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued a critical advisory on multiple vulnerabilities in Contec Health’s CMS8000 Patient Monitor, which pose serious risks such as remote attacks, data breaches, and unauthorized access. These flaws, with CVSS v4 scores reaching 9.3, could be exploited with minimal effort, threatening healthcare systems globally. The U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) has also issued a safety warning, emphasizing the severity of these security issues.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://gbhackers.com/malware-discovered-in-healthcare-patient-monitors/">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cisa.gov/resources-tools/resources/contec-cms8000-contains-backdoor]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>31 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Threat actors exploit .gov domains for phishing campaigns</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cofense Intelligence's report highlights the abuse of government (.gov) domains for phishing attacks from November 2022 to November 2024. Threat actors exploited these domains primarily for credential phishing and open redirects, leveraging trusted government URLs to bypass secure email gateways (SEGs). Open redirects, particularly those linked to CVE-2024-25608 in the Liferay platform, were a major vector of attack, allowing cybercriminals to redirect users to phishing sites. While U.S.-based .gov domains accounted for 9% of the cases, they were the third most exploited, with campaigns frequently mimicking Microsoft to steal credentials.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cofense.com/blog/threat-actors-exploit-government-website-vulnerabilities-for-phishing-campaigns]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>30 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Belgian airspace reopens, but flights still disrupted</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Belgian airspace has reopened after a technical problem at air traffic controller skeyes on Thursday afternoon. Flights to and from Brussels Airport are still reportedly disrupted. No planes were temporarily able to land or take off at Belgium's main airports, including Brussels Airport. At around 15:00, it emerged that the air traffic control system used by skeyes to operate Belgian airspace was "not functioning as required," said skeyes spokesperson Kurt Verwilligen.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.brusselstimes.com/belgium/1419037/belgian-airspace-closed-no-flights-to-land-or-take-off-across-country]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>30 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Wiz Research Uncovers Exposed DeepSeek Database Leaking Sensitive Information, Including Chat History</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>DeepSeek is the new AI solution that, since it was announced recently has made into the news. Wiz Research has identified a publicly accessible ClickHouse database belonging to DeepSeek, which allows full control over database operations, including the ability to access internal data. The exposure includes over a million lines of log streams containing chat history, secret keys, backend details, and other highly sensitive information. As DeepSeek made waves in the AI space, the Wiz Research team set out to assess its external security posture and identify any potential vulnerabilities.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.wiz.io/blog/wiz-research-uncovers-exposed-deepseek-database-leak]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>30 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>DeepSeek AI app blocked in Italy and investigated in Ireland</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On January 29, DeepSeek's AI Assistant app was removed from Apple and Google stores in Italy due to data privacy concerns. Italy’s data protection authority requested more details, while Ireland’s Data Protection Commission launched a GDPR investigation. Meanwhile, the US National Security Council announced a national security review of the app, raising further scrutiny over its data collection and privacy practices.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.reuters.com/technology/deepseek-app-unavailable-apple-google-app-stores-italy-2025-01-29/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>30 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russia-nexus APT possibly related to APT28 conducts cyber espionage on Central Asia and Kazakhstan diplomatic relations</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Since the start of the Ukraine war , the geopolitical landscape of Central Asia has undergone significant shifts, impacting the region's relationships with both Russia and China. Russia's influence, once dominant, has noticeably declined due to its actions in Ukraine, which have damaged its reputation as a regional security guarantor, with some Central Asian countries feeling that Russia doesn't respect their sovereignty.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Bitdefender Labs warns of an active cyber-espionage campaign targeting organizations in Central Asia and European countries. The group, tracked as UAC-0063, employs sophisticated tactics to infiltrate high-value targets, including government entities and diplomatic missions, expanding their operations into Europe.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://blog.sekoia.io/double-tap-campaign-russia-nexus-apt-possibly-related-to-apt28-conducts-cyber-espionage-on-central-asia-and-kazakhstan-diplomatic-relations/">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bitdefender.com/en-us/blog/businessinsights/uac-0063-cyber-espionage-operation-expanding-from-central-asia]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>30 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Hackers from China, Iran, and North Korea use AI tools to enhance cyberattacks On</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>January 29, The Wall Street Journal reported that hackers from China, Iran, and North Korea are using US AI products, including Google's Gemini, to enhance their cyberattacks. They appear to treat the platform more as a research assistant than a strategic asset, relying on it for tasks that boost productivity rather than developing new, advanced hacking techniques. These tools assist in tasks like reconnaissance and anomaly detection evasion.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/chinese-and-iranian-hackers-are-using-u-s-ai-products-to-bolster-cyberattacks-ff3c5884?mod=tech_lead_pos1]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>30 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>US Cyber Agency’s Future Role in Elections Remains Murky Under the Trump Administration</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has played a key role in securing election systems, but its future is uncertain amid Republican criticism and changes under the Trump administration. President Trump has not appointed a new leader for CISA, and Homeland Security Secretary Kristi Noem has suggested the agency has strayed from its core mission. Many Republicans, including Trump allies, accuse CISA of working with social media companies to censor conservative viewpoints on elections and health. The agency denies these claims, stating that it only helped notify platforms about misinformation but never coerced them to take action. Despite bipartisan praise from election officials for strengthening cybersecurity ahead of the 2020 and 2024 elections, CISA remains under political scrutiny.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Trump has signed an executive order to "end federal censorship" and investigate past actions, raising questions about CISA's role moving forward. A conservative policy proposal, Project 2025, suggests moving CISA to the Transportation Department and limiting its role to assessing states’ election cybersecurity rather than directly assisting them. This shift would significantly reduce CISA’s influence on election security, despite its success in helping states combat foreign interference since Russia's 2016 election meddling. Some election officials, initially skeptical of federal involvement, now acknowledge CISA’s contributions to strengthening voting systems, but the agency’s future remains uncertain under the new administration.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.securityweek.com/us-cyber-agencys-future-role-in-elections-remains-murky-under-the-trump-administration/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>30 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>UK Organizations Boost Cybersecurity Budgets</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>UK organizations are set to increase cybersecurity budgets by an average of 31% over the next year, more than double Gartner’s 15% forecast, according to Infosecurity Europe’s 2025 Cybersecurity Trends Report. While 75% of organizations expect budget growth, experts warn that higher spending does not always translate to better cyber resilience. Investment priorities include application security, network security, cloud security, and DevSecOps, driven by the rise of SaaS and rapid software deployment. However, 47% of cybersecurity leaders struggle to engage with boards, highlighting a disconnect between technical teams and strategic decision-making. The findings come as Infosecurity Europe marks its 30th anniversary, focusing on building a safer cyber world through collaboration, innovation, and education.	</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/news/uk-organizations-boosting/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>29 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Alleged Darkweb forum breach: 6,500+ NATO personnel data exposed.</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>!UNCONFIRMED!
			Older breach from mid-July, claimed by the attacker.  Data includes person, UUID, Modification date, Prefix, First/Middle/Last names, Portrait (not exported), Full Name, Countries, Organization, Function, Address, Phone numbers, Emails, Institution Members, Social Media (Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Instagram), Remarks, Biography, Textbox.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://x.com/cyberfeeddigest/status/1883784043604656250]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>29 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>NATO: There was officially a Russian plot to kill European weapons chief</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A senior NATO official has confirmed that there was a Russian scheme to kill Armin Papperger, the head of German arms manufacturer Rheinmetall.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The plot, which was foiled by United States and German intelligence, was part of a series of Russian plans to assassinate defense industry executives across Europe, according to NATO Deputy Assistant Secretary-General for Innovation, Hybrid, and Cyber James Appathurai.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.politico.eu/article/nato-official-confirms-russian-plot-kill-european-weapons-chief-armin-papperger/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>29 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Australia Invests $6.4M to Shield Healthcare Sector from Cyber Threats</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Australian government has announced a $6.4 million grant to the Critical Infrastructure – Information Sharing and Analysis Centre (CI-ISAC) Australia to establish a new cyber threat information-sharing network for the healthcare sector. This initiative comes in response to the increasing number of cyberattacks on healthcare organizations in Australia, including hospitals, health funds, and clinics.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thecyberexpress.com/australia-government-backs-healthcare/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>28 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Russian disinformation campaign targeting German election exposed</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On January 24, German investigative nonprofit Correctiv exposed a Russian disinformation campaign, attributed to the Russia-linked Storm-1516 threat actor, targeting Germany's February general election. Over 100 fake websites spread AI-generated false claims against politicians, including Green party candidate Robert Habeck and Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://correctiv.org/en/fact-checking-en/2025/01/24/disinformation-operation-russian-meddling-in-german-election-campaign-exposed/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>28 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Entire Georgian country population exposed in a massive data leak</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On January 27, 2025, cybersecurity researcher Bob Dyachenko and the Cybernews team discovered an unprotected Elasticsearch index hosted by a Germany-based cloud service provider, containing nearly five million personal data records of Georgian citizens, including ID numbers, full names, birth dates, genders, and phone numbers. The database was taken offline shortly after the discovery, but the exposure poses significant risks for the affected individuals.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://cybernews.com/security/entire-georgian-country-population-exposed/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>28 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>EU Sanctions Three Russians For 2020 Cyber-Attack on Estonia</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Three Russian nationals have been sanctioned by the EU for their involvement in a 2020 cyber espionage operation targeting Estonian government agencies. The Council said they breached several Estonian ministries, including Economic Affairs and Communications, Social Affairs and Foreign Affairs, and stole thousands of sensitive documents containing classified information. The sanctioned individuals will have all assets in EU countries frozen and been issued with a travel ban from the region. Additionally, any EU-based individuals and entities are banned on making funds available to those listed.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2025/01/27/cyber-attacks-three-individuals-added-to-eu-sanctions-list-for-malicious-cyber-activities-against-estonia/]]></link>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/news/eu-sanctions-russians-2020/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Baltic Sea data cable damaged in latest case of potential sabotage</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Disruption of line between Sweden and Latvia follows earlier incidents linked to Russia and China. The ship suspected to be responsible for the potential sabotage was captured by Sweden. Latvia's navy identified a suspect vessel, the Michalis San, near the location of the cable damage, along with two other ships. Naval tracking sites showed the Michalis San was en route to Russia. Sweden said Sunday that it seized a vessel suspected of damaging a fiber-optic cable under the Baltic Sea that links the country to Latvia, in what authorities are investigating as an act of "aggravated sabotage."</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>European Commission President Ursula Von der Leyen reiterated her pledges to improve the security of the bloc's critical infrastructure following reports that an undersea Baltic cable had been damaged.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2025/01/27/sweden-seizes-ship-suspected-of-damaging-baltic-sea-cable-a87744">Reference</a></p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.euractiv.com/section/politics/news/von-der-leyen-pledges-solidarity-after-latvia-sweden-undersea-cable-damage/">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.ft.com/content/b8765ad0-3e72-41b8-9915-da86b25de033]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cyber Attack Halts Operation of Supreme Administrative Court's in Bulgaria</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A cyber attack stopped the work of the information systems of the Supreme Administrative Court (SAC) and the administrative courts, as well as the SAC website, the press centre of the SAC said.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bta.bg/en/news/bulgaria/821969-cyber-attack-halts-operation-of-supreme-administrative-court-s-and-administrativ]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>After Bulgaria and Hungary last week, new bomb threats for schools in Slovenia and Bosnia-Hercegovina</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The HU and SI threats have many similarities. Like the email address starts with "fighter" translated to the local language, the first sentence translated to English of the email appears to be the same in both cases. No technical details are available from Bih.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2025/01/26/false-bomb-threats-lead-to-school-suspensions-in-bih">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.dnevnik.si/novice/kronika/zaradi-groznje-evakuirali-vec-slovenskih-sol-2714086/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>27 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>China's new cheap AI competes with the Western Giants</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>DeepSeek R1 is an innovative open source artificial intelligence model developed by DeepSeek, a Chinese company, which is making a sensation in the AI world. DeepSeek R1 has been praised by researchers for its ability to tackle complex reasoning tasks, particularly in mathematics and coding. The model employs a “chain of thought” approach similar to that used by ChatGPT o1, which lets it solve problems by processing queries step by step. Little is known about the lab and its founder, Liang WenFeng. DeepSeek was born of a Chinese hedge fund called High-Flyer Quant that manages about $8 billion in assets, according to media reports. Researchers claim that DeepSeek has built-in censorship.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.trendingtopics.eu/deepseek-this-is-what-live-censorship-looks-like-in-the-chinese-ai-chatbot/">Reference</a></p>
		<p></p>
		<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/24/how-chinas-new-ai-model-deepseek-is-threatening-us-dominance.html">Reference</a></p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.redhotcyber.com/post/e-guerra-aperta-sulle-ai-la-cina-sfida-con-deepseek-r1-i-giganti-statunitensi/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>A massive cyberattack against Slovakia is underway</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Another massive cyber attack against Slovakia is currently underway, this time targeting the General Health Insurance Company (VšZP), Slovak Prime Minister Robert Fico said at a press conference on Friday afternoon. He blamed Ukraine for the attack. Minister of Health Kamil Šaško added that the cyberattack continues, but so far all attempts to penetrate have been repelled. He assured the inhabitants of Slovakia that the provision of all services provided by VšZP is not threatened.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.novinky.cz/clanek/zahranicni-prave-probiha-masivni-kyberutok-proti-slovensku-oznamil-fico-40506156]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>The X page of FalconFeeds.io was hacked to display Bitcoin and Ethereum adverts</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cybersecurity / threat intelligence firm FalconFeeds.io has confirmed the attack. " We are aware that our X account Falcon Feeds has been compromised despite having 2FA enabled. We are actively investigating the incident and apologize for any inconvenience caused. Please note that recent crypto-related posts are scams, and we are in no way associated with them."	</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.linkedin.com/posts/falconfeedsio_we-are-aware-that-our-x-account-falcon-feeds-activity-7288418569749467136-lAKt]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>24 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Conduent confirms cybersecurity incident behind recent outage</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>American business services giant and government contractor Conduent confirmed today that a recent outage resulted from what it described as a "cyber security incident." Conduent has over 31,000 employees and provides services to half of Fortune 100 companies and over 600 government and transportation agencies. These include nine top U.S. health plans, four of five top global automakers, and multiple U.S. banks and pharma companies.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/conduent-confirms-cybersecurity-incident-behind-recent-outage/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>23 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Bomb threats in Bulgaria</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On 22th January, around a few 100 schools in Bulgaria also received bomb threats. The threats are also investigated by the Bulgarian cybercrime police.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://e-razgrad.bg/%D0%BA%D0%B8%D0%B1%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B0%D1%82%D0%B0%D0%BA%D0%B0%D1%82%D0%B0-%D1%81-%D0%B1%D0%BE%D0%BC%D0%B1%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B8%D1%82%D0%B5-%D0%B7%D0%B0%D0%BF%D0%BB%D0%B0%D1%85%D0%B8-%D0%B4%D0%BE%D1%81/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>23 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Think-tank warns of Russian meddling in German election</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On January 20, Reuters reported that the German think-tank CeMAS found that Russia is conducting a disinformation campaign on social media to influence Germany's upcoming election, aiming to boost the far-right Alternative for Germany (AfD) party and undermine mainstream parties. The campaign, which has typical patterns of Russia's Doppelgaenger and has reached over 2.8 million views, spreads false information and has been amplified by fake accounts.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russian-disinformation-targets-german-election-campaign-says-think-tank-2025-01-20/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>23 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Researchers say new attack could take down the European power grid</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Researchers have revealed critical vulnerabilities in Central Europe’s power grid infrastructure, which relies on unencrypted Radio Ripple Control signals to manage renewable energy facilities and streetlights. These signals, transmitted over radio frequencies, can be intercepted, recorded, and replayed by attackers to manipulate grid operations, potentially controlling up to 60 GW of power in Germany alone. The researchers demonstrated how malicious actors could theoretically exploit this system to destabilize the grid, potentially triggering widespread blackouts, though grid experts dispute the feasibility of such a catastrophic scenario. Despite this, the lack of encryption and outdated protocols like Radio Ripple Control underscore significant risks to critical infrastructure, with experts urging a transition to modern, secure alternatives such as LTE-based systems.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/01/could-hackers-use-new-attack-to-take-down-european-power-grid/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>23 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>New GhostGPT AI Chatbot Facilitates Malware Creation and Phishing</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Researchers at Abnormal Security have discovered a new malicious generative AI tool called GhostGPT, which is being sold on Telegram since late 2024. GhostGPT is designed to assist cybercriminals in executing various malicious activities, including malware creation, exploit development, and crafting convincing phishing and business email compromise (BEC) scams. Unlike prior tools such as WormGPT, WolfGPT, and EscapeGPT, GhostGPT simplifies access through a Telegram bot, eliminating the need for jailbreaking ChatGPT or configuring open-source large language models (LLMs).</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/news/ghostgpt-ai-chatbot-malware/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>23 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Bomb threatening in 268 Hungarian schools via email</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the bomb threats in Slovakia and Serbia in the autumn of 2024, on 23. January 2024 around 268 Hungarian schools have received bomb threats from the email address harcos@coredp.com.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Until the afternoon of 23th no devices were found in any institutions. Schools will resume in normal operation on the morning of 24th.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://telex.hu/belfold/2025/01/23/bombariado-magyarorszag-retvari-bence-orfk]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>23 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>US DHS dismisses Advisory Committees including the one investigating Salt Typhoon incidents</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The United States’ Department of Homeland Security (DHS) under the Trump administration dismissed all Advisory Committee members, including those of the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency’s (CISA) Cyber Safety Review Board (CSRB). The CSRB, tasked with reviewing major cybersecurity incidents, was actively investigating Salt Typhoon, the Chinese state-sponsored group linked to breaches in telecommunications networks. The decision, announced in a letter, was signed by acting DHS Secretary Benjamine C. Huffman and justified as a measure to avoid “misuse of resources”. The letter also stated that dismissed members could reapply for future roles in DHS committees, though no specifics were provided on which committees may be reconstituted or with whom.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-department-homeland-security-firing-all-advisory-committee-members-letter-2025-01-21/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>23 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Iran and Russia sign agreement to deepen military security and cyber cooperation</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Iran and Russia have formalized a new agreement to strengthen ties across military, security, and technological domains. Signed last week in Moscow by Russian President Vladimir Putin and Iranian President Masoud Pezeshkian, the agreement aims to elevate relations between the two heavily sanctioned nations. The two countries committed to expanding efforts to counter the use of information and communication technologies for criminal activities, agreed to exchange knowledge on managing national internet segments and to advocate for stricter global digital space controls, including imposing regulations on international tech companies. This treaty builds on prior agreements between the two nations, including a 2021 cyber cooperation pact that came into effect in August 2022. That agreement emphasized joint efforts in cybersecurity, prevention of cybercrime, and a mutual pledge not to engage in cyberattacks against one another.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[http://kremlin.ru/supplement/6258]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>22 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>New Star Blizzard spear-phishing campaign targets WhatsApp accounts</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Pro-Russian cyber threat actor Star Blizzard has shifted its tactics to target WhatsApp accounts in a spear-phishing campaign focused on government officials, diplomats, defense researchers, and entities aiding Ukraine. This campaign used emails impersonating U.S. government officials, tricking recipients into scanning QR codes that granted attackers access to WhatsApp messages via account linking. Although this campaign ended in November 2024, it demonstrates Star Blizzard's adaptability, leveraging new access methods to maintain its espionage activities. Microsoft and the U.S. Department of Justice previously disrupted Star Blizzard's operations by seizing over 180 phishing-related domains, but the group rapidly adapted. Targeted victim countries include the United States, Ukraine, and others indirectly involved in Russia-Ukraine-related diplomacy and research. Enhanced security measures, including advanced anti-phishing tools and endpoint detection, are recommended to mitigate such sophisticated threats.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/security/blog/2025/01/16/new-star-blizzard-spear-phishing-campaign-targets-whatsapp-accounts/?msockid=139ff52b6a70627739bfe0686b0f63df]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>22 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Cyber Threat Assessment for Denmark’s Water Sector</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Danish Center for Cybersecurity (CFCS) has published its first threat assessment on the cyber risks facing Denmark's water sector, a critical infrastructure responsible for drinking water and wastewater management. The report highlights the sector's vulnerability, citing a December 2024 cyberattack by pro-Russian activists that disrupted water supply for approximately 50 households by damaging a pipeline. CFCS warns of a very high threat level from cybercrime and moderate risks from cyber espionage, destructive attacks, and hacktivism, noting the global geopolitical situation's influence on the cyber domain. The assessment aims to help organizations in the water sector understand the threat landscape, strengthen risk management, and implement CFCS-recommended cybersecurity measures to safeguard systems and access points.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cfcs.dk/da/nyheder/2025/trusselsvurdering-for-vandsektoren/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>22 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Antonescu confirmed as PSD’s presidential candidate as tensions remain high</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Crin Antonescu, a member of Romania's National Liberal Party (PNL), has been confirmed as the presidential candidate for the PSD-PNL-UDMR governing alliance, despite internal opposition within the Social Democratic Party (PSD). His candidacy will be formally approved at the PSD congress on February 2. The upcoming presidential election, rescheduled after the annulment of the previous results by Romania’s Constitutional Court, is set for May 2025. Antonescu faces challenges in unifying his coalition and appealing to younger voters, as recent polls place him second with 25%, trailing Călin Georgescu at 38%. Notably, political tensions remain high, with potential rival candidates like Victor Ponta hinting at their ambitions.</p>]]> 	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/politics/news/antonescu-confirmed-as-psds-presidential-candidate-as-tensions-remain-high/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>22 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>US Big Tech backtracks on EU fact-checking commitments</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Major tech companies, including Google, Meta, TikTok, and Microsoft, are retreating from their commitments to the EU's Code of Practice on Disinformation, raising concerns about the future of fact-checking in the region. Google and Microsoft have indicated they will no longer support fact-checking for platforms like YouTube and Bing, citing existing measures or irrelevance to their services, while Meta has signaled potential shifts toward a community notes model. TikTok remains committed for now but conditioned its compliance on similar commitments from others. Civil society groups warn this trend undermines independent fact-checking and risks amplifying misinformation. This rollback comes as the EU prepares to enforce stricter disinformation regulations under the Digital Services Act (DSA) by mid-2025.</p>]]> 	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/tech/news/us-big-tech-backtracks-on-eu-fact-checking-commitments/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>US hits back at cyber threats with offensive operations</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On January 17, Politico reported on statements by Anne Neuberger, a senior Biden administration cyber official, who disclosed that the US had carried out secret offensive cyber operations against foreign adversaries targeting critical infrastructure. These classified measures aim to disrupt malicious networks and strengthen cybersecurity. Neuberger also emphasized the administration’s initiatives to address vulnerabilities, including a recent executive order requiring secure software for federal agencies.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://subscriber.politicopro.com/article/2025/01/biden-admin-quietly-hit-back-at-nations-that-targeted-the-u-s-with-cyberattacks-top-official-says-00198876]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>EU-based Trust Service Providers targeted in recent cyberattacks</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In January 2025, at least three EU-based Trust Service Providers (TSPs) reported on significant cybersecurity incidents resulting in potential data breaches. All three companies operate under the eIDAS Regulation (EU 910/2014), which governs electronic identification and trust services across the EU. No connection between the three incidents have been established at the time of writing.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[ENISA Flash report]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Spear-Phishing Campaign Targets WhatsApp Accounts in Ukraine</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Pro-Russian actor Star Blizzard has launched a new spear-phishing campaign targeting government, diplomacy, defense, international relations, and Ukraine aid organizations, as reported by Microsoft Threat Intelligence. The campaign, observed in November 2024, marks a shift in Star Blizzard’s tactics following the exposure and disruption of its earlier activities. The attack involves impersonating U.S. officials in phishing emails that invite targets to join WhatsApp groups supporting Ukraine, with a broken QR code designed to elicit a response. Victims are then sent a link to a fake WhatsApp invitation page where scanning a new QR code allows attackers to link their device to the victim's WhatsApp account. Without using malware, the attackers gain access to messages and can exfiltrate data through browser plugins.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/star-blizzard-hackers-abuse-whatsapp-to-target-high-value-diplomats/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Fake news about the Slovenian Prime Minister appeared on Facebook</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On Facebook, paid fake posts featuring doctored images and misleading text falsely claiming that Slovenian Prime Minister Robert Golob had been arrested by police appeared starting Wednesday. The posts, which mimicked the visual style of Slovenske novice, have since been removed, according to the government communication office. The fraudulent posts linked to an empty website registered anonymously in January 2024, suggesting an effort to discredit the government and sow instability in Slovenia.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://ljubljanainfo.com/novica/kronika/placane-lazne-vsebine-na-facebooku-tarca-je-bil-premier-robert-golob/269822#google_vignette]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Von der Leyen takes aim at China and signals to Trump in cautious Davos speech</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, in her speech at the World Economic Forum in Davos, emphasized the need for a balanced trade relationship with China, citing concerns over state-subsidized exports that disrupt global markets and undermine competition. She criticized China's economic policies, including subsidies for electric vehicles, which the EU countered with increased tariffs. Von der Leyen also highlighted the vulnerabilities of global supply chains, warning about their potential weaponization, such as in energy dependencies and cybersecurity risks, particularly targeting critical infrastructure like undersea data cables. Addressing U.S.-Europe trade ties, she underscored mutual economic interdependence, urging collaboration to safeguard economic and national security without undermining innovation and global prosperity.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/politics/news/von-der-leyen-takes-aim-at-china-and-signals-to-trump-in-cautious-davos-speech/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Ukrainian Hackers Attack Russian Financial Services</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Pro-Ukraine hacking group Yellow Drift targeted Roseltorg, a major Russian electronic trading platform integral to public procurement, defense contracts, and construction industries, in a significant cyberattack. Claiming responsibility, Yellow Drift stated they deleted 550 terabytes of data, including emails and backups, publishing evidence of their breach online. While Roseltorg reported full restoration of its systems, the attack disrupted operations, causing delays and concerns among users, including prominent Russian corporations and government agencies. This incident is part of a broader wave of cyberattacks by pro-Ukraine groups on Russian entities, highlighting vulnerabilities in critical infrastructure and the weaponization of cyber operations in geopolitical conflicts.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cybersecurityintelligence.com/blog/ukrainian-hackers-attack-russian-financial-services-8197.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>British Regulator Will Investigate Google</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The UK Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) has launched an investigation into Google's dominant market position in search and advertising, scrutinizing its impact on consumers, publishers, businesses, and rival search engines. Key areas under review include Google's search platform, its Google Ads service, and the role of its AI assistant, Gemini. With Google accounting for 90% of UK web searches and widely utilized for advertising, the CMA aims to determine if the company stifles competition or limits user choice. If violations are found, potential remedies could include data-sharing mandates or granting publishers greater control over how their content is used in Google's AI systems, addressing concerns over the integration of proprietary material in AI technologies. This investigation mirrors global scrutiny, as Google faces similar challenges in the U.S. and beyond regarding its practices in digital markets.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cybersecurityintelligence.com/blog/britsish-regulator-will-investigate-google-8192.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>21 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>US Sanctions Chinese Hackers for Treasury, Telecom Breaches (Salt Typhoon)</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. has imposed sanctions on Chinese state-backed cyber actors for their involvement in high-profile cyberattacks, including the December 2024 breach of the Department of the Treasury and the November 2024 compromise of U.S. telecom providers. Sanctioned entities include Yin Kecheng, implicated in the Treasury hack via a third-party vendor, and Sichuan Juxinhe Network Technology Co., Ltd, linked to the theft of sensitive call records and communications in a telecom attack orchestrated by the Salt Typhoon group. These actions highlight escalating Chinese cyber operations targeting U.S. infrastructure. The sanctions block U.S. assets of the designated parties and restrict transactions, aiming to disrupt their activities indirectly by limiting financial and logistical operations. Additionally, the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) has proposed stricter cybersecurity and supply chain requirements for telecom providers to bolster national communications security. These measures reflect a broader U.S. effort to counter cyber threats and safeguard critical infrastructure.	</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://osintcorp.net/us-sanctions-chinese-hackers-for-treasury-telecom-breaches/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 January, 2025></pubDate>
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Deputy MP wants Italian trains back on track</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Italy’s rail network is under scrutiny following incidents of suspected sabotage and significant service disruptions. Deputy Prime Minister and Infrastructure Minister Matteo Salvini announced plans to address parliament, citing "shocking episodes" reported by Italian State Railways. Among the incidents, a chain was discovered hanging from an overhead electrical system, risking severe damage to train pantographs and power lines, and an attempted break-in targeted a control unit. Rome prosecutors have launched an investigation into what appears to be deliberate interference, as reports indicate suspiciously frequent and coordinated malfunctions in critical areas.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The disruptions come amid a €100 billion railway modernization initiative, with over 1,200 active construction sites. Salvini has attributed current challenges to decades of mismanagement while defending the government's efforts to improve the rail system. However, the opposition has criticized Salvini, with former Prime Minister Matteo Renzi accusing him of mismanagement and calling for his resignation. The issue has sparked a political debate, adding pressure on Salvini as public frustration grows over the rail crisis.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.euractiv.com/section/politics/news/deputy-mp-wants-italian-trains-back-on-track/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Otelier data breach triggers serious data security concerns</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The hospitality industry is grappling with a significant cybersecurity incident involving Otelier, a popular data management software provider for major hotel chains such as Marriott, Hilton, and Hyatt. A breach occurred between July and October 2024, during which attackers stole over 8 terabytes of data stored in Amazon Web Services (AWS) storage buckets. The unauthorized access is suspected to have originated from compromised AWS credentials, potentially obtained through malware targeting an Otelier employee. Despite the scale of the breach, reports suggest no payment, employee, or operational data was affected.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Otelier, previously known as “MyDigitalOffice,” has temporarily suspended operations and engaged cybersecurity experts to investigate. Speculation indicates that the stolen data might include guest details, stay purposes, and contact information, which could be leveraged for phishing or identity theft. This breach underscores the critical need for robust cybersecurity measures in the hospitality sector to protect sensitive customer data and maintain trust. Recommendations include implementing strict data protection policies, employee training, network traffic monitoring, and encryption of sensitive information to mitigate future risks.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cybersecurity-insiders.com/otelier-data-breach-triggers-serious-data-security-concerns/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Anne Neuberger Steps Down as White House Cybersecurity Advisor: What’s Next for U.S. Cyber Defense?</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Anne Neuberger, Deputy National Security Advisor for Cyber and Emerging Technologies at the National Security Council, resigned on January 17, 2025, amidst heightened cybersecurity challenges in the U.S., particularly from China. Neuberger played a pivotal role in shaping the Biden administration's cybersecurity policies, including overseeing the U.S. Cyber Trust Mark program to improve consumer product security and guiding two significant cybersecurity executive orders. Her leadership helped address cyber threats targeting critical infrastructure such as power grids and communication networks.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>President Biden reinforced the administration's cybersecurity efforts with an executive order issued on January 18, 2025. This directive focuses on bolstering software and cloud security, mandating secure development practices for providers, and enhancing safeguards for federal systems. Agencies like NIST, CISA, and the OMB will enforce these standards while introducing policies for securing open-source software. These measures aim to address vulnerabilities highlighted by recent cyberattacks, including breaches like Salt Typhoon and incidents targeting the Treasury Department. Experts, including Robert Huber of Tenable Public Sector, praised these advancements for addressing supply chain security and rebuilding trust in U.S. cybersecurity infrastructure.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Beyond immediate cybersecurity threats, the administration is integrating resilience against climate change into its broader strategy. Officials from CISA have emphasized enhancing critical infrastructure to address environmental risks alongside national defense, reflecting a holistic approach to cybersecurity as an intersectional issue. As Neuberger departs, her legacy underscores the importance of sustained leadership and adaptive measures in addressing the evolving threat landscape.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thecyberexpress.com/neuberger-resigns-national-security-council/]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Salt Typhoon - The Chinese Telecom Hack – UPDATE</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Salt Typhoon cyberattack, attributed to Chinese state-sponsored actors, has emerged as one of the most significant cybersecurity incidents in U.S. history, targeting major telecommunications firms like AT&amp;T, Verizon, and T-Mobile. First disclosed in November 2024, the breach potentially compromised the cellular data of millions of Americans and highlighted the hackers' ability to maintain prolonged access to critical systems. Federal agencies, including the FBI, CISA, and NSA, alongside international partners from Australia, Canada, and New Zealand, are still investigating the attack's scope and objectives. Officials have confirmed the activity as a "persistent threat," with ongoing malicious activity and an uncertain timeline for full remediation.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The attack is part of a broader Chinese intelligence operation that has also targeted communications firms across Asia, Europe, and the MENA regions. The hack, involving advanced persistent threats (APTs) like Salt Typhoon, underscores the strategic value of telecommunications networks for espionage, destabilization, and geopolitical leverage. High-profile victims in the U.S. include presidential campaigns and Senate offices, raising national security alarms. Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas and Deputy National Security Adviser Anne Neuberger have called the breach highly sophisticated and deeply concerning.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>The incident has prompted calls for improved cybersecurity practices, including roader encryption use and stricter measures for protecting critical infrastructure. Experts emphasize the need for heightened vigilance among telecom providers and governments globally, as well as stronger collaboration with private cybersecurity firms like Microsoft and Mandiant to combat evolving threats. This breach also intensifies tensions between the U.S. and China over cyber-espionage and underscores the urgent need to fortify the resilience of digital infrastructure against nation-state attacks.</p>]]>
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://www.cybersecurityintelligence.com/blog/salt-typhoon-the-chinese-telecom-hack-whats-next-8189.html]]></link>
	</item>
	<item>
		<pubDate>20 January, 2025></pubDate>		
		<title><![CDATA[<h1>Budget 2025 on the Horizon: Will India Take the Leap in Enhancing Cybersecurity and Data Privacy?</h1>]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>India’s Union Budget 2025 is poised to play a transformative role in bolstering the nation’s cybersecurity framework as digital platforms and technologies become increasingly integral to business, governance, and daily life. Manish Mimani, CEO of Protectt.ai, highlights the urgency of addressing cybersecurity challenges by allocating resources for innovation, resilience, and skill development to safeguard India’s digital ecosystem. His recommendations focus on fostering innovation, enabling cost-effective security solutions, and developing a skilled cybersecurity workforce.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Key recommendations include establishing dedicated cybersecurity R&amp;D hubs across cities to drive innovation in homegrown security technologies and reduce dependency on foreign solutions. Mimani also emphasizes financial incentives for cybersecurity startups through tax holidays, grants, and subsidized loans to stimulate growth in this critical sector. Bridging the talent gap is another priority, with calls for comprehensive upskilling programs, subsidized training, and collaboration with educational institutions to attract and nurture cybersecurity talent.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>To encourage broader adoption of security practices, Mimani suggests reducing GST on Indian-made cybersecurity products and lowering import duties on essential hardware like servers and GPUs, making advanced technologies more accessible. Public-private partnerships could also accelerate the development of shared cybersecurity infrastructure, enabling threat intelligence sharing and innovation. Tax benefits for businesses implementing strong cybersecurity measures could further incentivize proactive defenses, ensuring a resilient digital economy.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>By integrating these measures into Budget 2025, India can enhance its defenses, foster technological innovation, and secure its position as a global technology hub while safeguarding its rapidly expanding digital ecosystem.</p>]]>	
		</description>
		<link><![CDATA[https://thecyberexpress.com/budget-2025-india-cybersecurity-data-privacy/]]></link>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>